My name is Mubeena Ali Khan.
Nama saya Mubeena Ali Khan.
I was working at NHM in South Block, Delhi, on contract basis.
Saya bekerja di NHM di South Block, Delhi, dengan status kontrak.
Last month, I submitted a sexual harassment complaint against Minister J.P. Sundaram
Bulan lalu, Saya mengajukan sebuah pelecehan seksual Pengaduan terhadap Menteri J.P. Sundaram
to my supervisor.
kepada atasan saya.
And I was fired the very next day.
Dan Saya dipecat keesokan harinya.
I have no idea how these UAPA charges were filed against me.
Saya tidak tahu Bagaimana ini tuduhan UAPA diajukan terhadap saya.
Other than organising rallies against Sundaram and his associates,
Selain Mengorganisir aksi Terhadap Sundaram dan rekan-rekannya,
the allegation that I conspired to assassinate him
tuduhan itu Saya bersekongkol untuk membunuhnya
is entirely baseless.
sama sekali tidak berdasar.
They said I accepted money from the opposition party to file the complaint.
Mereka berkata Saya menerima uang dari partai oposisi untuk mengajukan pengaduan.
While gathering evidence,
Saat mengumpulkan bukti,
the police discovered three messages in my mobile.
polisi Menemukan Tiga pesan di ponsel saya.
The first was a voice message.
Yang pertama adalah sebuah suara pesan.
in which someone from the opposition party
Di mana seseorang Dari partai oposisi
offered me ₹25 lakhs.
Menawarkan saya ₹25 lakh.
to make an allegation against JPS.
Ke buat sebuah tuduhan terhadap JPS.
Last week, a case was registered at Vellarada police station,
Lalu minggu, sebuah kasus terdaftar Di Vellarada polisi station,
where a fraudulent app scammed an expat of ₹1.5 crores.
Di mana sebuah fraudulent aplikasi Scammed sebuah ekspatriat dari ₹1.5 Crore.
He approached the cyber police,
Dia approached siber polisi,
but by then, the damage to his reputation was beyond repair.
Tapi oleh lalu, damage ke dia reputation melampaui repair.
When I saw that photo,
Kapan Saya melihat itu foto,
for a fraction of a second,
Untuk sebuah fraction dari sebuah detik,
I went completely blank.
Saya pergi sepenuhnya blank.
Normally, no one in government service would disclose something like this.
Biasanya, tidak ada orang di pemerintah layanan Akan disclose sesuatu suka ini.
But since it's you, I'll tell you this.
Tapi sejak itu kamu, Saya akan Beri tahu kamu ini.
Once we have a rough idea of the suspect,
Sekali kita sudah sebuah rough ide Dari tersangka,
we'll send a message to his phone through this Periscope software.
kita akan Kirim sebuah pesan ke dia telepon Melalui ini Periscope perangkat lunak.
Doesn't matter if he clicks it or not…
Tidak Urusan Jika dia klik itu atau tidak…
In our terms, we call it a "Zero-Click."
Di kita istilah, kita telepon itu sebuah "Nol-Klik."
We gain full control of the phone.
Kita memperoleh penuh kendali dari telepon.
A click gives us better accuracy.
Sebuah klik beri kita lebih baik accuracy.
Basically, once this application is installed on the phone,
Basically, sekali ini aplikasi dipasang di telepon,
its data consumption will increase.
Itu data consumption Akan increase.
By then, the application would be running continuously
Oleh lalu, aplikasi Akan menjadi berjalan terus-menerus
in the background of the consumer's phone.
Di background Dari consumer's telepon.
The phone will start heating up unusually.
Telepon Akan mulai Heating atas unusually.
The police claim
Polisi Claim
they found a conspiracy email on my laptop.
Mereka menemukan sebuah conspiracy email Di saya laptop.
At Brimstead Lab in London,
Di Brimstead Lab di London,
an investigation was conducted to uncover the truth.
Sebuah investigation conducted Ke uncover kebenaran.
That's when we realised
Itu Kapan kita sadar
that both my husband's phone and mine
Itu keduanya saya suami telepon Dan milik saya
were infected with the Periscope spyware.
terinfeksi dengan Periscope spyware.
What do honest people have to hide anyway?
Apa lakukan jujur orang harus Sembunyikan bagaimanapun?
This so-called privacy… it's not worth more than a human life, my friend.
Ini jadi-menelepon privasi… itu tidak worth Lebih daripada sebuah manusia hidup, saya teman.
So many lives have been affected by Periscope.
Jadi banyak hidup punya sudah Affected oleh Periscope.
Its misuse far outweighs its benefits.
Itu misuse jauh outweighs itu benefits.
Were you the one who initiated the purchase of this software?
Kamu satu siapa initiated purchase dari ini perangkat lunak?
I'm not asking this lightly.
Saya tidak menanyakan ini sembarangan.
I have seen documents.
Saya sudah Terlihat dokumen.
No comments!
Tidak comments!
[soulful rendition of Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram]
[Soulful rendition Dari Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram]
Gyan Chand Ji...
Gyan Chand Ji...
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
Namaste, Madam.
Namaste, Bu.
[in Hindi] How's your health?
[Di Hindi] Bagaimana kamu kesehatan?
[in Tamil] I'm fine, Sundaram.
[Di Tamil] Saya Baik, Sundaram.
The surgery can't be avoided.
Operasi tidak bisa menjadi avoided.
I tried your office many times.
Saya tried kamu kantor banyak waktu.
Why didn't you respond?
Kenapa tidak kamu tanggapi?
[in Tamil] Those are just allegations, Madam.
[Di Tamil] Itu hanya tuduhan, Bu.
I've already proved that in court.
Saya sudah Sudah terbukti itu di pengadilan.
Please don't misunderstand me unnecessarily.
Tolong jangan misunderstand saya Unnecessarily.
I am not here to discuss your personal stuff.
Saya tidak Sini ke bahas Kamu pribadi stuff.
In South Block,
Di South Block,
I too have ears, Sundaram.
Saya juga punya ears, Sundaram.
Using the government defence system to ensure your safety...
Menggunakan pemerintah pertahanan sistem Ke pastikan kamu keselamatan...
I don't think that's right.
Saya jangan pikir itu benar.
A software that was authorised during my term...
Sebuah perangkat lunak itu diizinkan Selama saya term...
Do you think it's fair to use that in a civilian case like this?
Lakukan kamu pikir itu adil ke gunakan itu Di sebuah warga sipil kasus suka ini?
You can always hide mentioning it as a classified document.
Kamu bisa Selalu sembunyikan mentioning itu Sebagai sebuah rahasia dokumen.
But for those running the government,
Tapi untuk itu berjalan pemerintah,
it is such a shame.
Itu seperti itu sebuah malu.
How long can you keep running from us, Sundaram?
Bagaimana lama bisakah kamu simpan Berjalan dari kita, Sundaram?
A total of eleven numbers!
Sebuah total dari eleven nomor!
1.5 crore rupees for each number!
1.5 Crore rupees untuk masing-masing nomor!
This isn't your family's money.
Ini tidak kamu keluarga uang.
In the next cabinet meeting,
Di berikutnya kabinet pertemuan,
I want answers on this.
Saya ingin jawab di sini.
Otherwise,
Sebaliknya,
I will not be silent as always!
Saya tidak akan menjadi silent sebagai selalu!
What is this, Madam?
Apa ini, Bu?
Are you threatening me now?
Apa kamu Threatening saya sekarang?
I've attended this function from this very spot
Saya sudah Attended ini function Dari ini sangat tempat
at least 15 times before you, right?
setidaknya 15 Waktu Sebelum kamu, benar?
The time for threats is over.
Waktu untuk ancaman atas.
Now, I need action.
Sekarang, Saya perlu action.
Madam, please. Don't get stressed. Think about your health.
Bu, tolong. jangan Dapatkan stres. Pikir tentang kamu kesehatan.
No.
Tidak.
I'm serious, Sundaram.
Saya Serius, Sundaram.
I need a response to my email,
Saya perlu sebuah tanggapan ke saya email,
the day I reach office after surgery!
hari Saya reach kantor Setelah operasi!
Understood?
Understood?
- Surgery date-- - Third. Next month.
- Operasi tanggal-- - Ketiga. Berikutnya bulan.
I will wait for that reply.
Saya akan Tunggu untuk itu balasan.
Ma'am, your bag, please.
Bu, kamu tas, tolong.
Okay. You may go.
Oke. Kamu boleh pergi.
- Ma'am! - Yes.
- Bu! - Ya.
Oh, good!
Oh, baik!
- Thank you, my girl. - Ma'am.
- terima kasih, Saya gadis. - Bu.
Fix me an appointment with Dr. Daniel, DRW.
Perbaiki saya sebuah appointment Dengan Dr. Daniel, DRW.
Okay, Madam.
Oke, Bu.
[in Hindi] Check if he's available tomorrow.
[Di Hindi] Periksa jika dia tersedia besok.
Okay.
Oke.
Oh... Yes!
Oh... Ya!
Wow!
Wow!
- Got you! - Good one!
- Mendapat kamu! - Baik satu!
- Namaste, sir. - I got that.
- Namaste, Pak. - Saya mendapat itu.
- Should I try again? - Yeah, sure.
- Harus Saya coba lagi? - Ya, yakin.
Okay?
Oke?
Ah!
Ah!
Can you please wait in the next room for some time?
Bisakah kamu Tolong tunggu di Berikutnya ruangan untuk beberapa waktu?
- Go on, son. - Come.
- Pergi di, anak laki-laki. - Datang.
Come on.
Ayo.
This is too official, Danny.
Ini Juga resmi, Danny.
Please sit!
Tolong duduk!
[in Malayalam] I've turned this into my office for a few days.
[Di Malayalam] saya sudah putar ini Ke dalam saya kantor untuk sebuah sedikit hari.
How are you doing now?
Bagaimana apa kamu melakukan sekarang?
I am fine. It's not that painful.
Saya Baik. Itu Tidak itu painful.
You know, I got him registered with the AIIMS list for transplant.
Kamu tahu, Saya mendapat dia terdaftar Dengan Aiims daftar untuk transplantasi.
[in Tamil] Your liver is non-alcoholic.
[Di Tamil] Kamu liver non-alkoholik.
Mine's severely alcoholic.
Milik saya severely alkoholik.
There is a difference, Madam.
Ada sebuah Perbedaan, Bu.
See? He always has an excuse!
Lihat? Dia selalu sudah sebuah permisi!
Do you recognise her?
Apa kamu Mengenali dia?
- Mrinalini Saha. - Yes, sir.
- Mrinalini Saha. - Ya, Pak.
PRO at NHM.
PRO di NHM.
And of course,
Dan tentu saja,
your most trusted insider!
Kamu paling percaya insider!
You're right.
Kamu Benar.
Mom...
Ibu...
Mom, please understand.
Ibu, tolong mengerti.
I'm okay.
Saya Oke.
Danny,
Danny,
I don't know what is happening with my phone.
Saya tidak tahu Apa terjadi Dengan telepon saya.
It's new, but the battery just won't last.
Itu Baru, tapi baterai Hanya tidak akan lalu.
It gets really hot too.
Itu dapatkan benar-benar hot juga.
Do you have time to take a look?
Apa kamu Punya waktu ke ambil sebuah lihat?
It's my official phone.
Itu Saya resmi telepon.
Mom is using too many apps, Sir.
Ibu menggunakan juga banyak aplikasi, Pak.
You should check her screen time.
Kamu harus Periksa dia layar waktu.
You didn't call me all the way here just to fix a phone!
Kamu tidak telepon saya semua cara sini Hanya ke perbaiki sebuah telepon!
Enough with the suspense.
Cukup dengan suspense.
What's the matter?
Apa urusan?
It's an MOU.
Itu Sebuah MOU.
An order from JPS.
Sebuah perintah dari JPS.
To hand over control of Periscope
Ke tangan atas kendali dari Periscope
to his own son's IT company,
Ke dia sendiri anak laki-laki IT perusahaan,
with immediate effect.
Dengan segera effect.
What does this mean?
Apa melakukan ini maksud?
I knew this was coming.
Saya tahu ini datang.
It's evident.
Itu Evident.
They are going to bring Social Score to people.
Mereka akan Bawa Sosial Skor ke orang.
So,
Jadi,
how does this affect?
Bagaimana melakukan ini affect?
Just like the CIBIL score assigned by banks to each of us,
Hanya suka Cibil skor Assigned oleh bank ke masing-masing dari kita,
JPS and his team
JPS dan dia tim
will rate individuals based on their social media conduct.
Akan rate individu berdasarkan Di mereka sosial media conduct.
To put it simply,
Ke taruh itu simply,
if a person dependent on government rations
Jika sebuah orang dependent Di pemerintah rations
posts a comment against JPS on social media,
Kiriman sebuah comment terhadap JPS di sosial media,
his family will starve!
Dia keluarga akan starve!
Hah!
Hah!
This is supposed to be a military spyware.
Ini Seharusnya ke menjadi Sebuah militer spyware.
How can they deploy this against civilians so casually?
Bagaimana bisa mereka deploy ini Terhadap warga sipil jadi casually?
This proves it, Madam.
Ini buktikan itu, Bu.
At the institution where I worked, until yesterday,
Di institution Di mana Saya bekerja, sampai kemarin,
this surveillance software required a three-layer security clearance.
Ini pengawasan perangkat lunak diperlukan Sebuah tiga-layer keamanan izin.
If it goes to the private sector, who's going to give the clearance?
Jika itu pergi ke pribadi sektor, Siapa akan beri izin?
- Sugar? - No.
- Sugar? - Tidak.
I'm going to oppose this in the next Cabinet meeting.
Saya akan Oppose ini Di berikutnya Kabinet pertemuan.
I'm forming a strong team against JPS...
Saya Forming sebuah strong tim Terhadap JPS...
with some powerful people.
Dengan beberapa powerful orang.
Danny, I need you to get us
Danny, Saya perlu kamu ke dapatkan kita
the list of phone numbers
daftar Telepon nomor
cleared by DRW for Periscope, as per JPS's instructions,
Jelas oleh DRW untuk Periscope, Sebagai per JPS's instruksi,
up to this date.
Atas ke ini tanggal.
We both are equally responsible for this.
Kita keduanya sama Bertanggung jawab untuk ini.
And in my team,
Dan di saya tim,
you will be my biggest confidant.
Kamu akan menjadi saya terbesar confidant.
In this fight...
Di sini lawan...
I don't know how far you'll succeed.
Saya tidak tahu Bagaimana jauh kamu akan succeed.
But you can count me in.
Tapi kamu bisa hitung saya di.
Sir, please sign here.
Pak, tolong sign sini.
Thank you, sir.
Terima kasih, Pak.
What is this?
Apa ini?
It's Daniel sir's bottle.
Itu Daniel Pak botol.
[in Tamil] Why so late?
[Di Tamil] Kenapa jadi terlambat?
Sorry, sir. There was traffic.
Maaf, Pak. Sana traffic.
You should've brought it faster.
Kamu harus'Ve membawa itu lebih cepat.
My hands are shaking already.
Saya tangan shaking sudah.
Everything is encrypted.
Semuanya terenkripsi.
You know the decryption pattern, right?
Kamu tahu decryption pola, benar?
Take it!
Ambil itu!
This much?!
Ini banyak?!
That's quite a lot, sir!
Itu Quite sebuah banyak, Pak!
Shut the door on your way out.
Diam pintu di kamu cara keluar.
[in Malayalam] I want this before your shift ends.
[Di Malayalam] Saya ingin ini Sebelum kamu giliran akhir.
Sir… could you at least give your signature for clearance…
Pak… bisa kamu setidaknya beri Kamu tanda tangan untuk izin…
I'll leave a mark on your face!
Saya akan Pergi sebuah tanda di kamu wajah!
Will that be enough clearance for you?
Akan itu menjadi cukup Izin untuk kamu?
- Tell me! - Sir! What is this, sir?
- Beri tahu saya! - Pak! apa ini, Pak?
Why do you think I put you on night shift?
Kenapa lakukan kamu pikir Saya taruh kamu di malam giliran?
So, infection could be confirmed with the latest Periscope Version 2.0.
Jadi, infeksi bisa menjadi dikonfirmasi Dengan terbaru Periscope Version 2.0.
The program has been reset three times in the past month.
Program sudah sudah reset Tiga waktu di masa lalu bulan.
The first reset happened on
Pertama reset terjadi di
January 30th, 3:20 PM IST.
January 30th, 3:20 PM IST.
Any possibility on the nature of the data taken?
Apa pun possibility di nature dari data diambil?
Was it WhatsApp data or contacts?
Itu WhatsApp data atau kontak?
No, Danny. That's not possible from our end.
Tidak, Danny. Itu Tidak mungkin dari kita akhir.
For us, the phone is completely compromised.
Untuk kita, telepon Sepenuhnya diretas.
Maybe, Ayesha can give you the date of it being self destructed.
Mungkin, Ayesha bisa beri kamu tanggal dari itu sedang diri destructed.
Yeah, that's already here.
Ya, itu sudah sini.
The second reset happened after two days by 8:00 PM
Detik reset terjadi Setelah dua hari oleh 8:00 PM
and the last reset...
Dan lalu reset...
was probably on the day it got uninstalled.
probably di hari Itu mendapat uninstalled.
February 7th, 12:30 PM IST.
February 7th, 12:30 PM IST.
Danny,
Danny,
what do you think of our teaching offer when you retire there?
apa yang kamu Pikir dari kita mengajar tawaran Kapan kamu retire sana?
We really think you should come over here and share your knowledge.
Kita benar-benar pikir kamu harus datang atas sini Dan bagikan kamu knowledge.
There's a lot you could do here.
Ada Sebuah banyak kamu bisa lakukan sini.
The campus is really good as well.
Campus benar-benar baik sebagai baiklah.
Danny, are you listening?
Danny, apa kamu dengar?
Yes.
Ya.
I'll have to think about it. Give me some time.
Saya akan harus Pikir tentang itu. Beri saya beberapa waktu.
So, Danny...
Jadi, Danny...
how's the victim of this infected phone?
Bagaimana korban Dari ini terinfeksi telepon?
She was recovering well after the surgery, sir.
Dia recovering baiklah Setelah operasi, Pak.
Even when you met her,
Bahkan kapan kamu bertemu dia,
she seemed fine and cheerful, didn't she?
Dia tampak baik Dan cheerful, tidak dia?
We took good care of her, didn't we?
Kita mengambil baik peduli Dari dia, tidak kita?
I didn't expect this infection.
Saya tidak berharap ini infeksi.
That's not the case.
Itu Tidak kasus.
She left only after fulfilling all her responsibilities.
Dia pergi hanya setelah fulfilling Semua dia tanggung jawab.
But some things still remain unfinished.
Tapi beberapa hal-hal Masih remain unfinished.
She's entrusted those responsibilities to me.
Dia Entrusted Itu tanggung jawab ke saya.
You should be proud of your mother.
Kamu harus Menjadi proud Dari kamu ibu.
Yes, sir.
Ya, Pak.
[Daniel] Was Madam's life meant to end like this?
[Daniel] Bu hidup Berarti ke akhir suka ini?
A brave woman who led the nation as a Minister for two terms.
Sebuah berani wanita siapa memimpin bangsa Sebagai sebuah Menteri untuk dua istilah.
This house is where I first saw a minister's office
Ini rumah di mana Saya pertama melihat Sebuah menteri kantor
functioning 24 hours a day.
Functioning 24 jam sebuah hari.
For the past ten years,
Selama Sepuluh tahun,
I had the privilege of serving as Madam's scientific advisor.
Saya sudah privilege dari melayani Sebagai Bu ilmiah penasihat.
She led several major missions that safeguarded the country.
Dia memimpin beberapa besar missions Itu safeguarded negara.
But in the end, within the same country's intelligence network,
Tapi di akhir, dalam sama Negara intelligence jaringan,
if she couldn't even use her own phone securely...
Jika dia tidak bisa bahkan gunakan Dia sendiri telepon securely...
imagine what awaits an ordinary civilian.
Bayangkan apa awaits Sebuah biasa warga sipil.
In a world fuelled by innovation,
Di sebuah dunia fuelled oleh innovation,
few rise to truly leave a mark.
Sedikit rise ke truly pergi sebuah tanda.
Mr. Shakti Sundaram is one such visionary.
Tn. Shakti Sundaram satu seperti itu visionary.
Under his trailblazing leadership,
Bawah dia trailblazing leadership,
Shakti Solutions is now more than a company.
Shakti Solusi sekarang Lebih daripada sebuah perusahaan.
And at the helm of it all,
Dan di helm dari itu semua,
Mr. Shakti Sundaram.
Tn. Shakti Sundaram.
Not just a founder,
Tidak hanya sebuah founder,
not just a chairman,
Tidak hanya sebuah chairman,
- but a pioneer... - Thank you.
- Tapi sebuah pioneer... - terima kasih.
...shaping tomorrow, today.
...Shaping besok, hari ini.
Let's welcome the man of the hour, Mr. Shakti Sundaram!
Biarkan sama-sama pria dari jam, Tn. Shakti Sundaram!
Perfect crowd for a perfect day!
Sempurna crowd untuk sebuah sempurna hari!
I... have always been called a nepokid.
Saya... Punya selalu sudah menelepon sebuah nepokid.
Thanks to Acha, my father,
Terima kasih ke Acha, saya ayah,
who gave me that name.
Siapa memberi saya itu nama.
Surprisingly,
Surprisingly,
I did not get into his way of serving the nation.
Saya tidak dapatkan ke dalam dia cara Dari melayani bangsa.
[Daniel] The first time I saw him,
[Daniel] pertama waktu Saya melihat dia,
he was just a kid running around South Block with his father.
Dia hanya sebuah kid berjalan sekitar South Block Dengan dia ayah.
And then one day, when I was teaching at DTA,
Dan lalu satu hari, Kapan Saya mengajar di DTA,
he was there among the cadets, just another average student.
Dia sana di antara cadets, Hanya lain average mahasiswa.
The next revolutionary service from Shakti Solutions...
Berikutnya revolutionary layanan Dari Shakti Solusi...
Ladies and gentlemen,
Ladies dan gentlemen,
"Samaj Seva"
"Samaj Seva"
The Social Evaluator!
Sosial Evaluator!
[Daniel] But the most memorable encounter...
[Daniel] Tapi paling memorable Encounter...
It's equally precious to both him... and me.
Itu Sama precious Ke keduanya dia... Dan saya.
Sir! Control Officer Ankit Rahane.
Pak! Kendali Petugas Ankit Rahane.
So, what is the situation now?
Jadi, apa situasi sekarang?
Sir, the FO has taken the flight above 30,000 ft.
Pak, FO sudah diambil penerbangan above 30,000 ft.
We are trying to bring him back to the base.
Kita Mencoba ke bawa dia Kembali ke basis.
Were you the Controlling Officer?
Kamu Controlling Petugas?
No, sir. It was Michael Devassy.
Tidak, Pak. Itu Michael Devassy.
A junior FC.
Sebuah junior FC.
A batch-mate with the FO at the Academy.
Sebuah angkatan-teman dengan FO Di Akademi.
And where is he now?
Dan di mana dia sekarang?
This is no time to stay away and cry.
Ini Tidak waktu Ke tinggal pergi dan menangis.
Brief me quickly. What happened?
Brief saya cepat. Apa yang terjadi?
Sir, I warned him multiple times.
Pak, Saya warned dia multiple waktu.
He exceeded the limit repeatedly.
Dia exceeded limit repeatedly.
Soon, he reported a fire inside the cockpit.
Segera, dia laporan Sebuah tembak di dalam kokpit.
Initially, I believed it was hypoxia.
Initially, Saya believed itu hypoxia.
He's had hallucinations before too, from low oxygen at high altitude.
Dia Sudah hallucinations sebelum juga, Dari rendah oksigen di tinggi ketinggian.
[Man] Viper reporting cockpit fire!
[Pria] Viper laporan kokpit tembak!
I repeat, cockpit fire!
Saya repeat, kokpit tembak!
Requesting permission for emergency landing!
Permintaan izin untuk pendaratan darurat!
Who is the Flight Officer?
Siapa Penerbangan Petugas?
Mayday! Mayday!
Mayday! Mayday!
Require permission for emergency landing!
Require izin untuk pendaratan darurat!
Shakti... Dr. Daniel here,
Shakti... Dr. Daniel sini,
from DRW.
Dari DRW.
- Are you listening? - [Shakti] Roger, sir.
- apa kamu Dengar? - [Shakti] Roger, Pak.
Requesting permission for emergency landing!
Permintaan izin untuk pendaratan darurat!
Please confirm your oxygen status.
Tolong konfirmasi kamu oksigen status.
Are you able to breathe?
Apa kamu Able ke bernapas?
Sir, I have lost my HUD!
Pak, saya sudah hilang saya HUD!
Zero visibility!
Nol visibility!
Losing my controls here, sir!
Losing saya kendali sini, Pak!
Shakti... Can you breathe? Answer that.
Shakti... bisakah kamu Bernapas? Jawab itu.
Yes, Sir. I can breathe.
Ya, Pak. Saya bisa bernapas.
Can you help me land, sir?
Bisakah kamu Tolong saya mendarat, Pak?
Shakti, listen to me.
Shakti, dengarkan saya.
I am not a pilot.
Saya tidak Sebuah pilot.
But I'm really familiar with the aircraft you're flying.
Tapi saya benar-benar familiar Dengan pesawat kamu flying.
You will now fly strictly as I instruct.
Kamu akan sekarang fly Ketat sebagai Saya instruct.
For that, I need your fullest cooperation.
Untuk itu, Saya perlu Kamu fullest cooperation.
Do you trust me?
Apa kamu percaya saya?
Shakti, come in.
Shakti, datang di.
Yes, sir! I trust you!
Ya, Pak! Saya percaya kamu!
I need the exact calculation of the fuel consumed by the aircraft since takeoff.
Saya perlu exact calculation dari bahan bakar Dikonsumsi oleh pesawat sejak takeoff.
- Immediately! - Sir.
- Segera! - Pak.
Shakti, listen. Now I'm trying to bring you back home.
Shakti, dengar. Sekarang saya mencoba ke Bawa kamu kembali rumah.
As per my indications here,
Sebagai per saya indications sini,
luckily there is no engine fire.
Untungnya ada tidak mesin tembak.
So don't panic.
Jadi jangan panik.
Reduce your altitude and maintain low speed.
Reduce kamu ketinggian Dan maintain rendah speed.
There's almost 2,800 litres of fuel left in the fuselage and wings.
Ada Hampir 2,800 litres dari bahan bakar pergi Di fuselage dan wings.
Danny, it's impossible to land the craft!
Danny, itu mustahil Ke mendarat craft!
Make him eject. There is no other option!
Buat dia eject. Ada Tidak lain option!
Kaushik...
Kaushik...
For me, the MIG is also important!
Untuk saya, MIG juga penting!
And there is a refinery in between.
Dan ada sebuah refinery di antara.
If he ejects now,
Jika dia ejects sekarang,
the MIG will crash exactly at that spot!
MIG akan crash Tepat di situ tempat!
Will you take the responsibility?
Akan kamu ambil tanggung jawab?
Shakti, now we're going to dump the fuel.
Shakti, sekarang kita pergi Ke buang bahan bakar.
That will make the aircraft lose its weight.
Itu akan buat pesawat Kehilangan itu weight.
- Are you ready? - [Shakti] Yes, sir!
- apa kamu Siap? - [Shakti] Ya, Pak!
Towards your left, in the emergency control panel,
Menuju kamu pergi, Di darurat kendali panel,
there is a Jettison lever.
ada sebuah Buang lever.
Sir... Zero visibility, sir!
Pak... Nol visibility, Pak!
Can you guide me?
Bisakah kamu Guide saya?
Shakti...
Shakti...
It's on the left side of your seat.
Itu Di pergi sisi dari kamu kursi.
Move your fingers down.
Bergerak kamu fingers turun.
You will find an L-shaped panel.
Kamu akan temukan sebuah L-shaped panel.
Can you see it?
Bisakah kamu Lihat itu?
The first round button on that panel.
Pertama round button di situ panel.
It is the Jettison switch.
Itu Buang switch.
Yes, sir. I got it.
Ya, Pak. Saya mendapat itu.
Press it.
Pers itu.
Minister JPS on the line.
Menteri JPS di baris.
FO's father.
FO's ayah.
You better speak to him.
Kamu lebih baik bicara ke dia.
Hello, sir.
Halo, Pak.
My only priority is to ensure Shakti lands safely, sir.
Saya hanya priority ke pastikan Shakti mendarat safely, Pak.
And he is responding well.
Dan dia tanggapi baiklah.
And I assure you, sir.
Dan Saya assure kamu, Pak.
I am going to bring him back safe to the base.
Saya Pergi untuk membawa dia kembali Aman ke basis.
Trust me on this, sir. Please.
Percaya saya di sini, Pak. Tolong.
Shakti, now take this as your training.
Shakti, sekarang ambil ini sebagai kamu pelatihan.
You are going to approach Mathura Refinery area.
Kamu akan Approach Mathura Refinery area.
That means... it's a two-kilometre no-fly zone.
Itu berarti... itu Sebuah dua-kilometre tidak-fly zone.
When your altitude reaches 1000 feet,
Kapan kamu ketinggian Reaches 1000 feet,
I'm going to make you do a barrel roll, belly up.
Saya akan Buat kamu lakukan Sebuah barrel roll, belly atas.
But sir, I have never done that before!
Tapi Pak, saya sudah tidak pernah selesai itu sebelum!
Then, let's do it now.
Lalu, biarkan lakukan itu sekarang.
Again... Do you trust me?
Lagi... apa kamu percaya saya?
Yes, sir!
Ya, Pak!
Now, push the throttle hard in the Z axis!
Sekarang, push throttle sulit Di Z axis!
Now, lift up and raise the altitude.
Sekarang, lift atas dan raise ketinggian.
Fast! Fast! Move! Move! Move!
Cepat! Cepat! Bergerak! Bergerak! Bergerak!
- This way! - Fast!
- Ini cara! - Cepat!
- To the front! - Keep it here!
- Ke front! - Simpan itu sini!
[Daniel] Normally, this would count as
[Daniel] Biasanya, Ini akan hitung sebagai
a training violation by a junior flight officer.
Sebuah pelatihan violation Oleh sebuah junior penerbangan petugas.
But I chose not to report it that way.
Tapi Saya chose tidak ke laporan itu itu cara.
Because deep down, I saw the grit in him to bring that flight back down
Karena deep turun, Saya melihat grit di dia Ke bawa itu penerbangan kembali turun
along with making it back alive.
Bersama dengan membuat itu kembali hidup.
But JPS stood against it.
Tapi JPS berdiri terhadap itu.
He sacrificed his son for his political future.
Dia sacrificed dia anak laki-laki Untuk dia political future.
He made him quit the force.
Dia membuat dia quit pasukan.
That was the end of Shakti's life in the force.
Itu akhir Dari Shakti hidup di pasukan.
What should we do now, sir?
Apa harus kita lakukan sekarang, Pak?
We'll have to shut down our office and hand the keys over to him, right?
Kita akan harus Diam turun kita kantor Dan tangan keys atas ke dia, benar?
Leave it, Danny.
Pergi itu, Danny.
Already...
Sudah...
We're already unable to deliver a lot of things on time.
Kita Sudah unable ke deliver Sebuah banyak dari hal-hal di waktu.
Let them share the burden.
Biarkan mereka bagikan burden.
What's wrong with that?
Apa salah dengan itu?
Periscope is an important program.
Periscope sebuah penting program.
A program that could easily be misused if it goes to the private sector.
Sebuah program itu bisa easily menjadi misused Jika itu pergi ke pribadi sektor.
I'll be forced to speak out.
Saya akan Menjadi forced ke bicara keluar.
You have turned into an old cynic, Danny.
Kamu punya putar ke dalam Sebuah lama cynic, Danny.
You should know your limits.
Kamu harus Tahu kamu limits.
Sir, with all due respect…
Pak, dengan semua due hormat…
I was among the very few who met Madam Nalini after her surgery.
Saya di antara sangat sedikit siapa bertemu Bu Nalini setelah dia operasi.
When it came to handing Periscope over to the Shakti Group,
Kapan itu datang ke tangan Periscope Atas ke Shakti Group,
she was the one who opposed it the most.
Dia satu Siapa opposed itu paling.
As per her request,
Sebagai per dia permintaan,
I procured the list of numbers JPS had ordered to be secretly spied on.
Saya procured daftar nomor JPS sudah memerintahkan ke menjadi secretly spied di.
And I...
Dan Saya...
still hold it.
Masih pegang itu.
Nalini Ramakrishnan did not die a natural death, sir.
Nalini Ramakrishnan tidak mati Sebuah natural kematian, Pak.
She was assassinated inside the hospital.
Dia assassinated Di dalam rumah sakit.
Stop it, Danny!
Berhenti itu, Danny!
I've seen the medical report too.
Saya sudah Terlihat medis laporan juga.
The reason of her death was an infection post surgery!
Alasan dari dia kematian sebuah infeksi kiriman operasi!
I can prove it, sir.
Saya bisa buktikan itu, Pak.
Because...
Karena...
that list included Nalini Madam's number as well!
Itu daftar included Nalini Bu nomor sebagai baiklah!
What's happening in your constituency?
Apa terjadi Di kamu constituency?
Huh?
Hah?
We gave you development funds, didn't we?
Kita memberi kamu development funds, tidak Kita?
Sir,
Pak,
I need five minutes of your time.
Saya perlu lima menit dari kamu waktu.
Daniel.
Daniel.
Periscope.
Periscope.
What do you think?
Apa yang kamu Pikir?
Will he negotiate?
Akan dia negosiasi?
No, sir. Never.
Tidak, Pak. Tidak pernah.
But as a government servant,
Tapi sebagai sebuah pemerintah servant,
he still comes under the Official Secrets Act.
Dia masih datang bawah Resmi Rahasia Bertindak.
Negotiation.
Negotiation.
National security.
Keamanan nasional.
If you're finding it difficult to look after Rahim,
Jika kamu temukan itu sulit Ke lihat setelah Rahim,
just inform the camp office and leave.
Hanya inform camp kantor Dan pergi.
I can take care of him myself.
Saya bisa ambil peduli dari dia myself.
There's no need to bring your kids here and cry about it.
Ada Tidak harus bawa Kamu anak-anak sini dan menangis tentang itu.
Sir, I'm not here to complain.
Pak, saya tidak sini ke complain.
These boys keep getting into trouble, and I'm the one left worried.
Ini anak laki-laki simpan mendapatkan ke dalam masalah, Dan saya satu pergi khawatir.
My husband has been on night shift since last week.
Saya suami sudah sudah di malam giliran Sejak lalu minggu.
So I bring them here at night.
Jadi Saya bawa mereka sini di malam.
At 9:30 PM, after Rahim sir falls asleep,
Di 9:30 PM, Setelah Rahim Pak jatuh asleep,
they somehow sneak into his room.
Mereka somehow sneak ke dalam dia ruangan.
I only found out about this when I saw the videos they shot on my phone.
Saya hanya menemukan keluar tentang ini kapan Saya melihat video mereka tembakan di telepon saya.
They used pictures from his room
Mereka digunakan pictures dari dia ruangan
and Rahim sir's medals to make videos
Dan Rahim Pak medals Ke buat video
and uploaded them to YouTube.
Dan diunggah mereka ke YouTube.
You're my only hope, sir.
Kamu Saya hanya hope, Pak.
If this gets reported to the camp office,
Jika ini dapatkan laporan Ke camp kantor,
I'll lose my job.
Saya akan Kehilangan saya pekerjaan.
Are these boys so notorious?
Ini anak laki-laki jadi notorious?
Where did they post it?
Di mana melakukan mereka kiriman itu?
We have our YouTube channel.
Kita sudah Kita YouTube channel.
Sandy & The Twins!
Sandy & Twins!
Sandy?
Sandy?
It's a dog in our area, sir.
Itu Sebuah dog di kita area, Pak.
That's what they call it.
Itu Apa mereka telepon itu.
Which channel is it?
Yang channel itu?
Let me have a look.
Biarkan saya punya sebuah lihat.
You have to subscribe, okay?
Kamu harus Subscribe, oke?
Okay.
Oke.
If Rahim Sir finds out, I'm done for!
Jika Rahim Pak temukan keluar, Saya Selesai untuk!
Your boys have put in a lot of effort.
Kamu anak laki-laki punya taruh di sebuah banyak dari effort.
Is this going to be a problem, sir?
Ini akan menjadi sebuah masalah, Pak?
I'll have my office staff remove the content.
Saya akan Punya saya kantor staff Hapus content.
But make sure they don't get hold of your phone again.
Tapi buat yakin mereka jangan dapatkan pegang Dari teleponmu lagi.
Okay.
Oke.
[Daniel] 1923 Official Secrets Act.
[Daniel] 1923 Resmi Rahasia Bertindak.
The offence involving possession of state secrets by a government official.
Offence involving possession dari negara bagian Rahasia oleh sebuah pemerintah resmi.
From today,
Dari hari ini,
I too am a dissident in their eyes.
Saya juga sebuah pembangkang Di mereka mata.
Vimathan [Dissident]
Vimathan [Pembangkang]
- Gaurav... - Yes?
- Gaurav... - Ya?
- [in Hindi] Pull the shutter down. - Okay, sir.
- [Di Hindi] Tarik shutter turun. - Oke, Pak.
I don't have much time.
Saya tidak punya Banyak waktu.
Transfer everything from this phone to this pen drive, fast.
Transfer semuanya dari ini telepon Ke ini pen drive, cepat.
Gaurav, give me your phone.
Gaurav, beri saya teleponmu.
- Hello? - Ayesha, this is Daniel.
- Halo? - Ayesha, ini Daniel.
Morning, Danny!
Pagi, Danny!
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
Dengar carefully ke apa saya tentang ke katakan.
I think my phone has been compromised
Saya pikir telepon saya Sudah sudah diretas
Danny, are you alright?
Danny, apa kamu baiklah?
Where are you now?
Di mana apa kamu sekarang?
I'm still in Delhi.
Saya Masih di Delhi.
I need a favour from you.
Saya perlu sebuah favour dari kamu.
You offered me a position in your university the other day, right?
Kamu menawarkan saya sebuah position di Kamu universitas lain hari, benar?
To teach Cyber Forensics?
Ke teach Siber Forensics?
Is it still available?
Itu masih tersedia?
Danny, I can't decide that alone.
Danny, Saya tidak bisa putuskan itu sendiri.
I should check with Scott.
Saya harus periksa dengan Scott.
Then please check with him immediately!
Lalu tolong periksa Dengan dia segera!
I don't have much time!
Saya tidak punya Banyak waktu!
If the position is available,
Jika position tersedia,
you should email me the offer letter at the earliest!
kamu harus Email saya surat tawaran Di earliest!
Right.
Benar.
I'll see what I can do.
Saya akan Lihat apa Saya bisa lakukan.
- Is it over? - Two minutes, sir.
- itu atas? - dua menit, Pak.
Gaurav, go check.
Gaurav, pergi periksa.
Move!
Bergerak!
Move aside!
Bergerak samping!
Sir,
Pak,
this drive is not recorded in the entry log.
Ini drive tidak rekam Di masuk log.
Sorry, sir. Sorry.
Maaf, Pak. Maaf.
Sir, Daniel's resignation has been confirmed.
Pak, Daniel resignation Sudah sudah dikonfirmasi.
It's already been emailed to the concerned authorities from his desk.
Itu Sudah sudah email ke Khawatir authorities dari dia desk.
Sir, Daniel has received an offer letter
Pak, Daniel sudah menerima Sebuah surat tawaran
from Brimstead University, London, for a teaching job.
Dari Brimstead Universitas, London, Untuk sebuah mengajar pekerjaan.
Check Daniel's UK visa validity.
Periksa Daniel UK visa validity.
Sir, the visa is valid till 2028.
Pak, visa valid till 2028.
Chances of Daniel exiting the country is imminent.
Kesempatan dari Daniel keluar negara imminent.
Issue a look-out notice for Dr. Daniel James
Masalah sebuah lihat-keluar perhatikan Untuk Dr. Daniel James
to all airports,
Ke semua bandara,
for violating the Official Secrets Act
Untuk violating Resmi Rahasia Bertindak
and trying to flee from the country!
Dan mencoba ke flee dari negara!
Excuse me, sir! One minute.
Permisi saya, Pak! Satu menit.
Sir, IB reports have confirmed...
Pak, IB laporan punya dikonfirmasi...
Daniel is on the London flight out of Kathmandu.
Daniel di London Penerbangan keluar dari Kathmandu.
We may have already lost him.
Kita boleh punya sudah hilang dia.
Vlog number 1.
Vlog nomor 1.
My name is Daniel James.
Nama saya Daniel James.
I've been a Scientific Advisor at DRW for the past 15 years.
Saya sudah Sudah sebuah Ilmiah Penasihat Di DRW selama 15 tahun.
But from today,
Tapi dari hari ini,
I will be known as "Vimathan" to you.
Saya akan Menjadi diketahui Sebagai "Vimathan" ke kamu.
I was inspired to make this video
Saya inspired ke buat ini video
by two eight-year-old boys.
Oleh dua delapan-tahun-lama anak laki-laki.
After working honestly within this system for so long,
Setelah bekerja honestly Dalam ini sistem untuk jadi lama,
I now realise I'm not even as brave as those boys.
Saya sekarang sadar saya tidak bahkan Sebagai berani sebagai itu anak laki-laki.
[Daniel] What I'm about to tell you
[Daniel] Apa saya tentang ke beri tahu kamu
could lead to my arrest when this flight lands.
Bisa pimpin ke saya tangkap Kapan ini penerbangan mendarat.
But I believe you'll watch this someday.
Tapi Saya percaya kamu akan lihat ini someday.
For a while now, I’ve been constantly faced with a single question.
Sebentar Sekarang, Saya’ve sudah constantly Faced dengan sebuah satu pertanyaan.
"Is my office using Periscope spyware or not?"
" saya kantor menggunakan Periscope spyware atau tidak?"
For them, this is my answer.
Untuk mereka, ini saya jawab.
When Nalini Ramakrishnan, who recently passed away, was my senior,
Kapan Nalini Ramakrishnan, Siapa recently passed pergi, saya senior,
this spyware was sanctioned for this very organisation...
Ini spyware sanctioned Untuk ini sangat organisation...
with my signature.
Dengan saya tanda tangan.
Back then, many of us, myself included, only looked at its positive aspects.
Kembali lalu, banyak dari kita, myself included, Hanya lihat di situ positive aspects.
But after a while, I realised
Tapi setelah sebuah saat, Saya sadar
Periscope had been installed on many phones,
Periscope sudah sudah dipasang Di banyak telepon,
including that of Nalini Madam, the very person who sanctioned the program.
Including itu dari Nalini Bu, sangat orang siapa sanctioned program.
The mastermind behind that move was a member of her own party,
Mastermind di belakang itu bergerak sebuah member dari dia sendiri partai,
cabinet minister JPS.
Kabinet menteri JPS.
Is there a secure internet connection I can use instead of public Wi-Fi?
Sana sebuah secure internet connection Saya bisa gunakan sebagai gantinya dari publik Wi-Fi?
I need to upload a video urgently.
Saya harus Upload sebuah video urgently.
The list of numbers that have been monitored through Periscope to date
Daftar Nomor itu punya sudah Dipantau melalui Periscope ke tanggal
by JPS for his personal gain…
Oleh JPS untuk dia pribadi memperoleh…
I'm releasing it now.
Saya Releasing itu sekarang.
You can access them through the link below and examine them.
Kamu bisa Akses mereka melalui tautan Bawah dan examine mereka.
Many on that list are no longer alive,
Banyak di situ daftar tidak longer hidup,
including Nalini Ramakrishnan.
Including Nalini Ramakrishnan.
And the ones who are alive, you better stay alert.
Dan satu siapa hidup, Kamu lebih baik tinggal alert.
You're all being watched.
Kamu Semua sedang lihat.
You are all under surveillance!
Kamu Semua bawah pengawasan!
I don't have to answer this.
Saya tidak perlu jawab ini.
This is nothing new.
Ini Tidak ada baru.
Enemy states have long attempted to target our people.
Enemy negara bagian punya lama attempted Ke target kita orang.
Daniel is one such individual who fell into their trap.
Daniel satu seperti itu individu Siapa fell ke dalam mereka trap.
Unfortunately,
Sayangnya,
he is a traitor to our country.
dia Sebuah pengkhianat ke kita negara.
No matter which country he hides in, we will get him.
Tidak urusan yang negara dia sembunyikan di, Kita akan dapatkan dia.
And we will bring him back and put him on trial.
Dan kita akan bawa dia kembali Dan taruh dia di trial.
- Thank you! - [reporters shouting questions]
- terima kasih! - [Reporters berteriak pertanyaan]
Please move! Move back!
Tolong bergerak! Bergerak kembali!
Vlog number 112.
Vlog nomor 112.
Vimathan here!
Vimathan sini!
Most of the requests in my inbox
Paling dari permintaan di saya inbox
were for my review of the X-7.
untuk saya review dari X-7.
Like I always say,
Suka Saya selalu katakan,
this isn't a paid review.
Ini tidak sebuah paid review.
Please don't decide to buy or not buy this phone based on what I say here.
Tolong jangan putuskan ke beli atau tidak beli Ini telepon berdasarkan di apa Saya katakan sini.
So, let's begin.
Jadi, biarkan begin.
This is my first impression.
Ini Saya pertama impression.
If you buy this phone,
Jika kamu beli ini telepon,
you'll be travelling around with the biggest spy in your pocket.
kamu akan Menjadi travelling sekitar Dengan terbesar spy di kamu pocket.
I say this because its camera
Saya katakan ini karena itu kamera
keeps tracking and reporting your location without you even knowing.
Simpan lacak dan laporan kamu Lokasi tanpa kamu bahkan tahu.
The main villain behind it is this connection.
Utama villain di belakang itu ini connection.
If you want to take photos, buy a camera.
Jika kamu mau ke ambil foto, Beli sebuah kamera.
Why buy a phone?!
Kenapa beli sebuah telepon?!
This one is the next villain.
Ini satu berikutnya villain.
Even if your phone is off, as long as the battery still has charge,
Bahkan jika teleponmu mati, sebagai lama Sebagai baterai masih sudah tuduhan,
it will keep sharing your location.
Itu akan simpan sharing kamu lokasi.
This feature is more useful
Ini feature lebih useful
to those tracking you, than to you.
Ke itu lacak kamu, Daripada ke kamu.
Now, let's move to the microphone.
Sekarang, biarkan bergerak ke microphone.
What you see here
Apa kamu lihat sini
is the most advanced military graded transmitter.
paling advanced Militer graded transmitter.
Whenever you discuss travel plans, bank loans,
Kapan pun kamu bahas Travel rencana, bank pinjaman,
or hotel bookings, with anyone,
Atau hotel bookings, dengan siapa pun,
this one will immediately notify the relevant parties.
Ini satu akan segera notify relevant parties.
Your next concern might be that the phone's resale value will drop
Kamu berikutnya concern mungkin menjadi itu telepon'S resale value akan jatuhkan
if you remove these components, right?
Jika kamu hapus ini Components, benar?
If possible, don't trade in your old phone for a new one.
Jika mungkin, jangan trade di Kamu lama telepon untuk sebuah baru satu.
Because you'll be selling your own life along with your phone.
Karena kamu akan menjadi selling kamu sendiri hidup Bersama dengan teleponmu.
No matter how many factory resets you do,
Tidak urusan bagaimana banyak Factory reset kamu lakukan,
if there's something valuable to you on that phone,
Jika ada sesuatu valuable Ke kamu di situ telepon,
someone who knows how to take it will definitely take it!
Seseorang siapa tahu bagaimana ke ambil itu Akan definitely ambil itu!
Now,
Sekarang,
to those who think that they don't give a damn if they lose their privacy…
Ke itu siapa pikir itu mereka jangan Beri sebuah sial jika mereka kehilangan mereka privasi…
I'll share the story of a 16-year-old girl who lost her privacy, knowingly or not.
Saya akan Bagikan cerita dari sebuah 16-tahun-lama gadis Siapa hilang dia privasi, knowingly atau tidak.
An 11th-grade student from Kadamakkudy Panchayat in Ernakulam district.
Sebuah 11th-nilai mahasiswa dari Kadamakkudy Panchayat di Ernakulam district.
The crime she committed was that she sold nude pictures of herself
Crime dia committed itu Dia sold nude pictures dari herself
to a criminal network abroad for a very high price.
Ke sebuah penjahat jaringan abroad Untuk sebuah sangat tinggi price.
Unable to cope with the shame, her father took his own life.
Unable ke cope dengan malu, Dia ayah mengambil dia sendiri hidup.
Local police found evidence against her
Local polisi menemukan Bukti terhadap dia
from the laptop she was using.
Dari laptop dia menggunakan.
She received this laptop on merit through a government scheme
Dia menerima ini laptop di merit Melalui sebuah pemerintah skema
for securing an A+ in 10th grade.
Untuk securing sebuah Sebuah+ di 10th nilai.
These free laptops come with several pre-installed apps.
Ini bebas laptop datang Dengan beberapa pre-dipasang aplikasi.
There was one application that caught my attention among them.
Sana satu aplikasi Itu caught saya perhatian di antara mereka.
I had seen that application before… at one of DRW's official summits.
Saya sudah terlihat itu aplikasi sebelum… Di satu dari DRW's resmi konferensi.
There is another side to this which most people are unaware of.
Ada Lain sisi ke ini Yang paling orang tidak sadar dari.
At first, the girl's father had taken an online loan for her education.
Di pertama, gadis ayah sudah diambil Sebuah online pinjaman untuk dia education.
And in the end… they sent him his own daughter's secret!
Dan di akhir… mereka mengirim dia Dia sendiri anak perempuan rahasia!
The parent company behind that loan app… is Shakti Solutions.
Orang tua perusahaan di belakang Itu pinjaman aplikasi… Shakti Solusi.
The very same company supplied those free laptops!
Sangat sama perusahaan supplied Itu bebas laptop!
How did a defence application end up on a schoolgirl's laptop?
Bagaimana melakukan sebuah pertahanan aplikasi Akhir atas di sebuah schoolgirl's laptop?
So, as far as I'm concerned, that girl is innocent.
Jadi, sebagai jauh sebagai saya khawatir, Itu gadis innocent.
This is for the police to investigate,
Ini Untuk polisi ke investigate,
and Shakti Corporation must answer for it!
Dan Shakti Perusahaan Harus jawab untuk itu!
Aren't you Daniel?
Tidak Kamu Daniel?
I am a big fan of yours, sir.
Saya Sebuah besar fan dari milikmu, Pak.
My son studies at your college.
Saya anak laki-laki studi di kamu kampus.
Mathew, third semester, Architecture.
Mathew, ketiga semester, Architecture.
Oh!
Oh!
I don't know him.
Saya tidak tahu Dia.
Don't you have a police case back home?
Jangan Kamu punya sebuah polisi kasus Kembali rumah?
Easy to sit here and talk crap about people back home, right?
Mudah ke duduk sini dan bicara crap Tentang orang kembali rumah, benar?
Commit fraud there and come hide here like nothing happened, right?
Commit fraud sana dan datang sembunyikan sini Suka tidak ada terjadi, benar?
What do you want now?
Apa yang kamu Ingin sekarang?
I was just saying, sir.
Saya hanya katakan, Pak.
This is... that Pakistani girl, right?
Ini... Itu Pakistani gadis, benar?
Are you still with her, sir?
Apa kamu Masih dengan dia, Pak?
I married her!
Saya menikah dia!
Got a problem with that? Get lost!
Mendapat sebuah masalah dengan itu? Dapatkan hilang!
Who was that?
Siapa itu?
A fan!
Sebuah fan!
You've been invited to a YouTubers' summit
Kamu sudah Sudah invited Ke sebuah YouTubers' konferensi
organised by a Malayali association in Faraha.
Organised oleh sebuah Malayali association Di Faraha.
Take a look at the sponsors.
Ambil sebuah lihat di sponsors.
Are they really shameless enough to invite me to this?
Mereka benar-benar shameless cukup Ke invite saya ke ini?
People think deleting a file
Orang pikir deleting sebuah file
makes it disappear.
Buat itu disappear.
Truth is...
Kebenaran...
nothing really goes away.
Tidak ada benar-benar pergi pergi.
It just hides...
Itu hanya sembunyikan...
until someone looks for it.
Sampai seseorang lihat untuk itu.
See you on Monday.
Lihat kamu di Monday.
And... don't hack my Wi-Fi again!
Dan... jangan Hack saya Wi-Fi lagi!
94, 95, 96,
94, 95, 96,
97, 98, 99...
97, 98, 99...
100!!!
100!!!
Congrats, sir!
Congrats, Pak!
Even with 1 million or 100 million followers,
Bahkan dengan 1 million Atau 100 million pengikut,
you're still going to pay for what you've done!
kamu Masih akan bayar Untuk apa kamu sudah selesai!
Run and hide in London all you want,
Lari dan sembunyikan di London semua kamu mau,
but say one more word against JPS
Tapi katakan satu lebih word terhadap JPS
and I'll come there, butcher you,
Dan saya akan datang sana, Butcher kamu,
sever your head and dump it right outside your Pakistani woman's door.
Sever kamu kepala dan buang itu Benar di luar kamu Pakistani wanita pintu.
Aren't you ashamed to betray your motherland
Tidak Kamu ashamed Ke betray kamu motherland
and live with random women, you dog?
Dan hidup dengan random women, kamu dog?
Hey, don't stop the party!
Hei, jangan berhenti partai!
We are used to this.
Kita Digunakan ke ini.
I'll go refill this.
Saya akan Pergi refill ini.
- Hello? - Is this Radhakrishnan?
- Halo? - ini Radhakrishnan?
Yes.
Ya.
I am Daniel.
Saya Daniel.
Who?
Siapa?
Daniel. Vimathan! Vimathan!
Daniel. Vimathan! Vimathan!
Haven't you had enough, you scumbag?
Belum Kamu sudah cukup, Kamu scumbag?
You work in the Electricity Board, right?
Kamu kerja di Electricity Naik, benar?
Is the strike finally over there?
Strike akhirnya atas sana?
Your wife still works at LIC, right?
Kamu istri masih kerja di LIC, benar?
Hey, don't try your nasty tricks!
Hei, jangan coba kamu nasty tricks!
Why do you care where I work?
Kenapa apa kamu peduli di mana Saya kerja?
You have two children, right?
Kamu punya dua anak-anak, benar?
Shalini, the elder one,
Shalini, elder satu,
is a first-year engineering student in Kottayam.
sebuah pertama-tahun engineering mahasiswa Di Kottayam.
Right?
Benar?
Are you taking a census of my family?
Apa kamu Mengambil Sebuah census dari saya keluarga?
That's your government's job, isn't it?
Itu Kamu pemerintah pekerjaan, tidak itu?
Shalini is having dinner at the CSI hostel right now.
Shalini punya dinner Di CSI asrama sekarang juga.
My people are near the hostel.
Saya orang near asrama.
You! You!
Kamu! Kamu!
Should I ask them to walk into the hostel and meet her?
Harus Saya tanya mereka ke jalan Ke dalam asrama dan temui dia?
If you touch my daughter...
Jika kamu touch saya anak perempuan...
They won't touch her.
Mereka tidak akan touch dia.
They'll just kill her.
Mereka akan Hanya bunuh dia.
I've got people in Pakistan too.
Saya sudah Mendapat orang di Pakistan juga.
You know that, right?
Kamu tahu Itu, benar?
Hello?
Halo?
Radhakrishnan... Are you there?
Radhakrishnan... Apa kamu Sana?
Dear sir...
Sayang Pak...
I am sorry!
Saya Maaf!
Please don't hurt my daughter!
Tolong jangan sakit saya anak perempuan!
Okay.
Oke.
Will you do as I say, Radhakrishnan?
Akan kamu lakukan sebagai Saya katakan, Radhakrishnan?
I will! I'll do whatever you want!
Saya akan! saya akan Lakukan apa pun kamu mau!
Then delete the video you sent me today.
Lalu hapus video Kamu mengirim saya hari ini.
Sir, I didn't do it alone.
Pak, Saya tidak lakukan itu sendiri.
Others were involved. It's been sent to some groups too.
Lain involved. Itu Sudah mengirim ke beberapa grup juga.
Okay… delete it from everywhere it's been sent… then call me.
Oke… hapus itu dari everywhere itu Sudah mengirim… lalu telepon saya.
I'll update you about your daughter then… okay?
Saya akan Pembaruan kamu Tentang kamu anak perempuan lalu… oke?
Just messing around!
Hanya messing sekitar!
Dear sir,
Sayang Pak,
the person who used this phone
orang siapa digunakan ini telepon
is no longer alive.
tidak longer hidup.
The answer to the question in your last vlog...
Jawab ke pertanyaan Di kamu lalu vlog...
is in this phone.
di sini telepon.
If you are convinced,
Jika kamu convinced,
let's connect.
Biarkan connect.
Used by Jyothi Kurian, 28 years,
Digunakan oleh Jyothi Kurian, 28 tahun,
Data Analyst, Shakti Solutions.
Data Analyst, Shakti Solusi.
♪ Who gently came and opened my heart's closed door? ♪
♪ Siapa gently datang dan buka Saya heart's closed pintu? ♪
♪ Was it a breeze I've never felt before? ♪
♪ itu sebuah breeze Saya sudah Tidak pernah felt sebelum? ♪
♪ Who crossed this lonely land of longing silently through? ♪
♪ Siapa melewati ini lonely mendarat dari lama Silently melalui? ♪
♪ Was it you? ♪
♪ itu kamu? ♪
♪ O heart, your doors have opened their eyes ♪
♪ O heart, kamu pintu Punya buka mereka mata ♪
♪ All on their own at the wind's soft sighs ♪
♪ Semua di mereka sendiri Di wind's lembut sighs ♪
♪ You blossomed bright in joyful desire ♪
♪ Kamu blossomed bright Di joyful keinginan ♪
♪ From head to toe like glowing fire ♪
♪ Dari kepala ke toe Suka glowing tembak ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday ke kamu ♪
Sir?
Pak?
Jyothi, you handled the Students' Laptop Scheme allotment, right?
Jyothi, kamu handled Siswa' Laptop Skema allotment, benar?
Yes, sir.
Ya, Pak.
The family of one of those students is creating trouble at the reception.
Keluarga dari satu dari itu siswa creating masalah di reception.
Get here quickly.
Dapatkan sini cepat.
Enough talking!
Cukup bicara!
- What's the matter? - Who are you, girl?
- Apa urusan? - siapa kamu, Gadis?
- I'm Jyothi. I'm the Data-- - Are you in charge here or not?
- saya Jyothi. saya Data-- - apa kamu Di tuduhan sini atau tidak?
Yes. I'm the Data Analyst here.
Ya. saya Data Analyst sini.
Whatever the issue is, we can talk it through.
Apa pun masalah, Kita bisa bicara itu melalui.
- Please don't create a scene. - This is the girl's mom.
- Tolong jangan create sebuah adegan. - ini Gadis ibu.
[Michael] Who are those people? You are okay, right?
[Michael] Siapa itu orang? Kamu Oke, benar?
My daughter got her laptop from here.
Saya anak perempuan mendapat dia laptop dari sini.
She studies really well and works really hard.
Dia studi benar-benar baiklah Dan kerja benar-benar sulit.
She's been in jail for 16 days now, dear.
Dia Sudah di penjara untuk 16 hari sekarang, sayang.
The police are saying she sent something from her laptop she was not supposed to.
Polisi katakan dia mengirim sesuatu Dari dia laptop dia tidak seharusnya ke.
They're not even granting her bail.
Mereka Tidak bahkan granting dia jaminan.
You're the one who did everything for us, right?
Kamu satu siapa melakukan Semuanya untuk kita, benar?
Please help us.
Tolong tolong kita.
I understand, Chechi.
Saya mengerti, Chechi.
I was only responsible for the laptop allotment. Beyond that--
Saya hanya bertanggung jawab untuk laptop allotment. Melampaui itu--
Don't beat around the bush and waste our time.
Jangan Beat sekitar bush Dan waste kita waktu.
It's our girl who's in jail.
Itu Kita gadis siapa di penjara.
We're not leaving until this is sorted out!
Kita Tidak leaving Sampai ini sorted keluar!
Chetta, what I'm saying is...
Chetta, apa saya katakan...
I can't say anything without checking that laptop.
Saya tidak bisa katakan apa pun Tanpa periksa itu laptop.
It's with the police, dear.
Itu Dengan polisi, sayang.
Our lawyer filed petitions twice to get it back.
Kita pengacara diajukan petitions Twice ke dapatkan itu kembali.
But they refused, saying we might destroy the evidence.
Tapi mereka refused, katakan kita mungkin Destroy bukti.
How can I say anything without checking the laptop?
Bagaimana bisa Saya katakan apa pun Tanpa periksa laptop?
Listen… Two other students from our ward have received the same laptops.
Dengar… Dua lain siswa dari kita bangsal Punya menerima sama laptop.
Can you at least check those?
Bisakah kamu setidaknya Periksa itu?
I'm reaching there. Sheeba is with me.
Saya Reaching sana. Sheeba dengan saya.
Nothing to worry, okay?
Tidak ada ke worry, oke?
Shall we go to the other student's place now?
Kita pergi Ke lain Siswa tempat sekarang?
Do you know anything about this program, Mike?
Lakukan kamu tahu apa pun Tentang ini program, Mike?
This is the only thing I found unusual.
Ini Hanya hal Saya menemukan tidak biasa.
At least tell me now.
Setidaknya Beri tahu saya sekarang.
What is this program?
Apa ini Program?
Is this something I'm not meant to know?
Ini sesuatu Saya tidak Berarti ke tahu?
If that's the case, I'll find another way.
Jika itu kasus, Saya akan Temukan lain cara.
What do you want to know?
Apa yang kamu ingin tahu?
I just want to know if that girl is in jail because of this program.
Saya hanya ingin tahu jika itu gadis di penjara karena dari ini program.
How many students are using laptops from our scheme?
Bagaimana banyak siswa menggunakan Laptop dari kita skema?
Did any of them get into any sort of trouble?
Melakukan apa pun dari mereka dapatkan Ke dalam apa pun sort dari masalah?
Why are you so sure it's not her mistake?
Kenapa apa kamu jadi yakin itu Tidak dia kesalahan?
Because I went to their house.
Karena Saya pergi ke mereka rumah.
The photos they say she leaked are of her changing clothes!
Foto mereka katakan dia leaked dari dia changing clothes!
In houses like theirs, if someone needs to change,
Di rumah suka milik mereka, Jika seseorang perlu ke ubah,
the others have to step out.
lain harus langkah keluar.
What else would be in the house at that time?
Apa lagi Akan menjadi Di rumah di situ waktu?
Just the laptop… sitting on a table or chair!
Hanya laptop… Sitting di sebuah table atau chair!
Is this program secretly watching them?
Ini program Secretly lihat mereka?
Jyothi, please!
Jyothi, tolong!
Don't get too invested in this.
Jangan Dapatkan juga invested di sini.
Ultimately, we are all working for a corporate firm!
Ultimately, kita semua bekerja Untuk sebuah corporate firm!
Why do we need a job that ruins ordinary people's lives?
Kenapa lakukan kita perlu sebuah pekerjaan Itu ruins biasa orang hidup?
What if this is just the first case?
Apa jika ini hanya pertama kasus?
What if more students end up facing such a problem?
Apa jika lebih siswa akhir atas Facing seperti itu sebuah masalah?
This issue isn't as serious as you think.
Ini masalah tidak sebagai serius Sebagai kamu pikir.
How do SOS emergency programs work on our phones?
Bagaimana lakukan SOS darurat program Kerja di kita telepon?
This works the same way.
Ini kerja sama cara.
You know it's a government scheme, right?
Kamu tahu itu Sebuah pemerintah skema, benar?
These laptops are intended to benefit underprivileged students.
Ini laptop intended ke benefit Underprivileged siswa.
Unfortunately,
Sayangnya,
the areas these end users come from have high child abuse rates.
area ini akhir users datang dari Punya tinggi anak abuse rates.
The demand for such a program came to our team from the official side…
Demand untuk seperti itu sebuah program Datang ke kita tim dari resmi sisi…
for precautionary measures.
Untuk precautionary measures.
That means,
Itu berarti,
this application can remotely access the laptop's camera, right?
Ini aplikasi bisa remotely akses laptop kamera, benar?
Don't just walk off. Explain, Mike!
Jangan Hanya jalan mati. Jelaskan, Mike!
I told you already, right?
Sudah saya bilang Sudah, benar?
Only under certain circumstances,
Hanya bawah tertentu circumstances,
for public safety,
Untuk publik keselamatan,
we can access that program. That's all!
Kita bisa akses itu program. Itu Semua!
Here you can see all the students' academic records
Sini kamu bisa lihat Semua siswa' academic rekam
and their loan applications in detail.
Dan mereka pinjaman aplikasi di detail.
Explain this, Jyothi.
Jelaskan ini, Jyothi.
What were you doing at Michael's cabin in the night?
Apa kamu melakukan di Michael cabin di malam?
You're not authorised to access this floor.
Kamu Tidak diizinkan Ke akses ini floor.
And if you say Michael asked you to come,
Dan jika kamu katakan Michael Bertanya kamu ke datang,
he wasn't even in the office then!
Dia tidak bahkan di kantor lalu!
You care to explain?
Kamu peduli ke jelaskan?
You either explain or we'll have to terminate you.
Kamu salah satu jelaskan Atau kita akan harus terminate kamu.
Hey, bro!
Hei, bro!
Hi, Shakti.
Hai, Shakti.
Listen, Mike...
Dengar, Mike...
I don't care if you're sleeping with her or not.
Saya jangan peduli jika kamu sleeping Dengan dia atau tidak.
But I need to know what information you've shared with her.
Tapi saya harus tahu apa informasi kamu sudah Dibagikan dengan dia.
Shakti, I don't understand.
Shakti, Saya jangan mengerti.
You know better than I do
Kamu tahu Lebih baik daripada Saya lakukan
why this program runs on those student laptops.
Kenapa ini program lari di Itu mahasiswa laptop.
Yesterday, that girl used your ID to access the top floor.
Kemarin, itu gadis digunakan kamu ID Ke akses top floor.
So, how can I ignore?
Jadi, bagaimana bisa Saya ignore?
You might have shared some information with her!
Kamu mungkin punya dibagikan Beberapa informasi dengan dia!
Jyothi was Shakti's point of contact for the free laptop scheme.
Jyothi Shakti poin dari contact Untuk bebas laptop skema.
So when a student's family came here with a complaint, she followed it up. That's all.
Jadi kapan sebuah siswa keluarga datang sini Dengan sebuah pengaduan, dia ikuti itu atas. itu Semua.
Then why the hell did she meet their lawyer?
Lalu kenapa hell melakukan dia Temui mereka pengacara?
Listen, Mike. She has some sensitive information from your computer.
Dengar, Mike. Dia sudah beberapa sensitive Informasi dari kamu komputer.
If that gets out,
Jika itu dapatkan keluar,
you know the consequences, right?
kamu tahu consequences, benar?
What would Jyothi even get from my computer?
Apa akan Jyothi bahkan dapatkan Dari saya komputer?
Just some data analytics and program information.
Hanya beberapa data analytics Dan program informasi.
What can she even do with that?
Apa bisa dia bahkan lakukan dengan itu?
Mike, Mike, Mike...
Mike, Mike, Mike...
Hang on.
Hang di.
What if...
Apa jika...
she turns against us?
Dia putar terhadap kita?
She's figured out we do consumer profiling…
Dia Figured keluar kita lakukan Consumer profiling…
and that we're monitoring individual data.
Dan itu kita pemantauan Individu data.
Are you sure she won't go to court and speak about this program?
Apa kamu Yakin dia tidak akan pergi ke pengadilan Dan bicara tentang ini program?
Shakti... Hey...
Shakti... Hei...
She won't do such a thing.
Dia tidak akan lakukan seperti itu sebuah hal.
I'll talk to her and make her understand.
Saya akan Bicara ke dia Dan buat dia mengerti.
That's up to you, bro.
Itu Atas ke kamu, bro.
I don't want someone like that in Shakti Group anymore.
Saya tidak mau Seseorang suka itu Di Shakti Group lagi.
Even after she's fired,
Bahkan setelah dia dipecat,
it's your responsibility to make sure
itu Kamu tanggung jawab Ke buat yakin
she keeps her mouth shut.
Dia simpan dia mulut diam.
I've been calling you since this morning.
Saya sudah Sudah menelepon kamu Sejak ini pagi.
You haven't been answering my calls!
Kamu belum sudah Jawab saya telepon!
Why don't you just stay out of this issue, Jyothi?
Kenapa jangan kamu hanya Tinggal keluar dari ini masalah, Jyothi?
For that, you need to think from my perspective, Michael.
Untuk itu, kamu harus pikir Dari saya perspective, Michael.
You're not an activist.
Kamu Tidak sebuah activist.
A company has its own policies on how to run its business.
Sebuah perusahaan sudah itu sendiri policies Di bagaimana ke lari itu business.
We have to understand that and work within that!
Kita harus mengerti itu Dan kerja dalam itu!
I can't do that, Mike!
Saya tidak bisa lakukan itu, Mike!
They're just 15 or 16-year-old school kids!
Mereka Hanya 15 atau 16-tahun-lama Sekolah anak-anak!
What do they even know?
Apa lakukan mereka bahkan tahu?
How many more parents do I have to face?
Bagaimana banyak lebih orang tua Lakukan saya harus wajah?
What am I supposed to tell them?
Apa Saya seharusnya ke beri tahu mereka?
That we'll give your kids free laptops for their studies,
Itu kita akan beri kamu anak-anak Bebas laptop untuk mereka studi,
but your lives will be under our company's control?
Tapi kamu hidup akan menjadi bawah Kita perusahaan kendali?
Jyothi, please try to understand what I'm saying.
Jyothi, tolong coba ke mengerti Apa saya katakan.
Do you think what you did was right?
Lakukan kamu pikir Apa kamu melakukan benar?
You breached into my system!
Kamu breached ke dalam saya sistem!
Do you think they'll just let this go?
Lakukan kamu pikir mereka akan Hanya biarkan ini pergi?
They will ruin your career!
Mereka akan ruin kamu career!
I know...
Saya tahu...
you are one of them.
kamu Satu dari mereka.
Aren't you?
Tidak Kamu?
So that's why you didn't answer my calls.
Jadi itu kenapa Kamu tidak jawab saya telepon.
- Right? - See!
- Benar? - Lihat!
You've also started behaving like them, Michael.
Kamu sudah Juga mulai behaving Suka mereka, Michael.
I never expected anything from this relationship.
Saya tidak pernah berharap apa pun Dari ini relationship.
So, don't expect anything from me either!
Jadi, jangan berharap apa pun Dari saya salah satu!
And I didn't answer your calls...
Dan Saya tidak jawab kamu telepon...
because my phone's battery doesn't last.
Karena telepon saya's baterai tidak Lalu.
They...
Mereka...
They're monitoring your phone.
Mereka Pemantauan teleponmu.
A microwave can cancel the radio frequency.
Sebuah microwave bisa cancel radio frequency.
Get a new phone.
Dapatkan sebuah baru telepon.
You should be safe.
Kamu harus Menjadi aman.
That's all I want.
Itu Semua Saya ingin.
What do I even have to hide?
Apa lakukan Saya bahkan harus sembunyikan?
Am I supposed to stop living, fearing a phone?
Saya seharusnya ke berhenti hidup, Fearing sebuah telepon?
Let them take whatever they want!
Biarkan mereka ambil Apa pun mereka ingin!
How can I run away from this?
Bagaimana bisa Saya lari pergi dari ini?
Come with me.
Datang dengan saya.
Hello sir...
Halo Pak...
This is Michael.
Ini Michael.
I know you didn't send me this phone just to show me your life with Jyothi.
Saya tahu kamu tidak kirim saya ini telepon Hanya ke tunjukkan saya kamu hidup dengan Jyothi.
You wanted me to know what she knew.
Kamu ingin saya ke tahu Apa dia tahu.
In that case,
Di situ kasus,
I need to know what happened to her after that as well.
Saya harus Tahu apa yang terjadi Ke dia setelah itu sebagai baiklah.
Nothing much happened in her life after that, sir.
Tidak ada banyak terjadi Di dia hidup setelah itu, Pak.
The next day,
Hari berikutnya,
she came to the office as usual.
Dia datang ke kantor sebagai usual.
Since she was on her notice period,
Sejak dia di dia perhatikan period,
she had a lot of pending work.
Dia sudah sebuah banyak dari pending kerja.
Even then,
Bahkan lalu,
she took sick leave
Dia mengambil sick pergi
and left early.
Dan pergi early.
Around 4 PM
Sekitar 4 PM
her room-mate called me…
Dia ruangan-teman menelepon saya…
saying Jyothi had collapsed in the bathroom.
Katakan Jyothi sudah collapsed Di bathroom.
By the time they got her to the hospital, she had passed away.
Oleh waktu mereka mendapat dia ke rumah sakit, Dia sudah passed pergi.
When you last saw Jyothi,
Kapan kamu lalu melihat Jyothi,
did you notice anything unusual about her?
Melakukan kamu perhatikan apa pun Tidak biasa tentang dia?
I didn't want to see her like that, sir.
Saya tidak ingin ke lihat dia Suka itu, Pak.
We didn't part on good terms.
Kita tidak bagian di baik istilah.
A video of her was shared in the office WhatsApp group.
Sebuah video dari dia dibagikan Di kantor WhatsApp grup.
I never...
Saya tidak pernah...
even opened it.
Bahkan buka itu.
Can I see those videos?
Bisa Saya lihat itu video?
We got an invite for that YouTubers' summit in Faraha, right?
Kita mendapat sebuah invite untuk itu YouTubers' konferensi di Faraha, benar?
Did you respond to them?
Melakukan kamu tanggapi ke mereka?
No.
Tidak.
It's happening next week.
Itu Terjadi berikutnya minggu.
Shall we go for it?
Kita pergi Untuk itu?
Why the sudden change of mind?
Kenapa sudden ubah dari pikiran?
Shakti Group is giving me a space to speak at their own event!
Shakti Group giving saya sebuah space Ke bicara di mereka sendiri acara!
Why should I miss this chance?
Kenapa harus Saya miss ini kesempatan?
That's up to you.
Itu Atas ke kamu.
I also think you should go, Danny.
Saya juga pikir kamu harus pergi, Danny.
How long are you going to stay cooped up indoors?
Bagaimana lama apa kamu pergi Ke tinggal cooped atas indoors?
But strictly no controversies in your speech!
Tapi ketat tidak controversies Di kamu speech!
No controversy at all.
Tidak controversy di semua.
Just simple talk.
Hanya simple bicara.
Reply to them and confirm my acceptance.
Balasan ke mereka Dan konfirmasi saya acceptance.
Let's go.
Ayo pergi.
Okay.
Oke.
Right now, some of the world's top vloggers are here,
Sekarang juga, Beberapa dari dunia Top vloggers sini,
showcasing their skills.
Showcasing mereka skills.
I'm so thrilled to be part of this...
Saya Jadi thrilled Ke menjadi bagian dari ini...
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
Next!
Berikutnya!
I have 14K followers. I'm into lifestyle content--
Saya sudah 14K pengikut. Saya Ke dalam lifestyle content--
Do you like pranks?
Apa kamu Suka lelucon?
Oh, I love them! It's so exciting!
Oh, Saya cinta mereka! Itu Jadi exciting!
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
Yo! Vimathan!
Yo! Vimathan!
He speaks from a room that has forgotten its own walls.
Dia bicara dari sebuah ruangan Itu sudah forgotten itu sendiri walls.
Every surface, they say, Has become an ear
Setiap surface, mereka katakan, Sudah become sebuah ear
Every silence, they say, Is being collected
Setiap diam, mereka katakan, Sedang collected
He invented windows to look at the world
Dia invented jendela Ke lihat di dunia
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
But now, it seems, the windows are watching him
Tapi sekarang, itu sepertinya, jendela lihat dia
It seems the wind that gushes in through those windows,
Itu sepertinya wind itu gushes Di melalui itu jendela,
absorbs his secrets along with his sweat
Absorbs dia rahasia Bersama dengan dia sweat
His name is "Human"
Dia nama "Manusia"
Been a while since I got into a government vehicle.
Sudah sebuah saat sejak Saya mendapat ke dalam Sebuah pemerintah vehicle.
- You won't rat me out, right? - Come on, sir.
- Kamu tidak akan rat saya keluar, benar? - ayo, Pak.
This is a different country.
Ini sebuah Berbeda negara.
Who's going to mess with you here, sir?
Siapa akan mess Dengan kamu sini, Pak?
Don't worry.
Jangan Worry.
Contrary to what the media back home claims, she's not Pakistani.
Contrary ke apa media Kembali rumah claims, dia tidak Pakistani.
She's from Chavakkad. A pure Malayali!
Dia Dari Chavakkad. Sebuah pure Malayali!
She just has UK citizenship. That's all.
Dia hanya sudah UK citizenship. Itu Semua.
- Ayesha. - Raghu.
- Ayesha. - Raghu.
You shouldn't be afraid to go back home.
Kamu tidak seharusnya menjadi afraid Ke mundur rumah.
They can't do squat to you, sir.
Mereka tidak bisa lakukan squat ke kamu, Pak.
Easy for you to say that sitting here!
Mudah untuk kamu ke katakan itu Sitting sini!
Ever since I moved away from our country,
Pernah sejak Saya pindah pergi Dari kita negara,
my health got better.
Saya kesehatan mendapat lebih baik.
I don't drink like I used to. I'm not stressed anymore.
Saya jangan minum suka Saya digunakan ke. Saya tidak Stres lagi.
None of this is our country's fault.
None dari ini kita negara fault.
It's the fault of certain people who control it.
Itu fault dari tertentu orang Siapa kendali itu.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Saya Jadi maaf, Pak.
All the sea-view rooms are already occupied.
Semua sea-view ruangan sudah occupied.
Just a room to sleep in. Can we get one?
Hanya sebuah ruangan ke sleep di. Bisa kita dapatkan satu?
I'll get back to you.
Saya akan Dapatkan kembali ke kamu.
Laughter in one room, becomes entertainment for another house
Laughter di satu ruangan, Becomes entertainment untuk lain rumah
A wail in one room, Becomes news in another
Sebuah wail di satu ruangan, Becomes berita di lain
Your mind, and all it holds,
Kamu pikiran, dan semua itu pegang,
is nothing but an open file on someone's desk.
tidak ada tapi sebuah buka file Di seseorang desk.
Were shadows kept on sale all this while?
Shadows kept di sale Semua ini saat?
Were thoughts being measured?
Pikir Sedang measured?
Were gadgets always strategies?
Gadgets selalu strategies?
♪ O, Alien Oasis... O, garden of illusions and secrets ♪
♪ O, Alien Oasis... O, garden dari illusions dan rahasia ♪
♪ Have the butterflies arrived in soft delusions ♪
♪ Punya butterflies tiba Di lembut delusions ♪
♪ Unaware of the fire, drawn by desire ♪
♪ Tidak sadar dari tembak, Ditarik oleh keinginan ♪
- Oh! Vimathan! - Hey!
- Oh! Vimathan! - Hei!
♪ Only to be consumed by that fire ♪
♪ Hanya ke menjadi dikonsumsi Oleh itu tembak ♪
The room was never a room,
Ruangan tidak pernah sebuah ruangan,
but a stall in a farm.
Tapi sebuah stall di sebuah peternakan.
For someone to milk dry, and when yield fails, to be slaughtered
Untuk seseorang ke milk kering, Dan kapan yield fails, ke menjadi slaughtered
Not a dystopian animal farm.
Tidak sebuah dystopian animal peternakan.
But where he, his kind,
Tapi di mana dia, dia jenis,
you, and I all reside:
Kamu, dan Saya semua reside:
A real Human Farm.
Sebuah nyata Manusia Peternakan.
We don't build companies.
Kita jangan bangun companies.
We build wars, disguised as business.
Kita bangun perang, Disguised sebagai business.
Productivity is not in the excel sheets.
Productivity tidak Di excel sheets.
It's about how many battles we win before breakfast!
Itu Tentang bagaimana banyak battles kita menang Sebelum breakfast!
Sir, Daniel has started with his presentation.
Pak, Daniel sudah mulai Dengan dia presentation.
Okay, guys. Let's pick it up tomorrow.
Oke, teman-teman. Biarkan pick itu atas besok.
Make sure I have the reports tonight.
Buat yakin saya sudah laporan malam ini.
Aparna, I want the feed here.
Aparna, Saya ingin feed sini.
But he's not someone any of us can ignore.
Tapi dia tidak seseorang Apa pun dari kita bisa ignore.
Let's welcome the brutally honest Vimathan!
Biarkan sama-sama brutally jujur Vimathan!
It's been a long time
Itu Sudah sebuah lama waktu
since I've seen my fellow countrymen like this in person.
Sejak saya sudah terlihat saya fellow countrymen Suka ini di orang.
You might say, “We're expats too!”
Kamu mungkin katakan, “kita Ekspatriat juga!”
Yes, that's true.
Ya, itu benar.
But there's a difference between us.
Tapi ada sebuah perbedaan Antara kita.
All of you are expats who came here to work,
Semua dari kamu ekspatriat Siapa datang sini ke kerja,
still upholding your allegiance to our country.
Masih upholding kamu Allegiance ke kita negara.
But what about me?
Tapi apa tentang saya?
I'm an expat who had to flee that country
Saya Sebuah ekspatriat Siapa sudah ke flee itu negara
after forsaking the same allegiance.
Setelah forsaking sama allegiance.
Most of you may not know my real name, Daniel James.
Paling dari kamu boleh tidak tahu Saya nyata nama, Daniel James.
I was given the name "Vimathan" or Dissident,
Saya diberi nama "Vimathan" atau Pembangkang,
by Shakti Corporation.
Oleh Shakti Perusahaan.
So, at an event hosted by them,
Jadi, di sebuah acara hosted oleh mereka,
if I don't speak at least a few words about them,
Jika Saya jangan bicara setidaknya Sebuah sedikit words tentang mereka,
that wouldn't be fair.
Itu tidak akan menjadi adil.
When Shakti Group was founded as an IT consultancy back in 2017,
Kapan Shakti Group menemukan Sebagai sebuah IT consultancy kembali di 2017,
their balance sheet stood at a mere ₹20,000.
Mereka balance sheet berdiri Di sebuah mere ₹20,000.
By 2021-22,
Oleh 2021-22,
that figure had grown to ₹80 crores.
Itu figure sudah grown Ke ₹80 crore.
And the company's current assets are valued at…
Dan perusahaan current assets valued di…
₹1,600 crores!
₹1,600 Crore!
There's no magic behind this success.
Ada Tidak magic Di belakang ini success.
Just a clear vision with a futuristic approach.
Hanya sebuah jelas vision Dengan sebuah futuristic approach.
Yes, just one click.
Ya, hanya satu klik.
A single click on your phone!
Sebuah satu klik di teleponmu!
This is the secret behind that single click.
Ini Rahasia Di belakang itu satu klik.
Signed in 2021 between the government and Shakti…
Ditandatangani di 2021 antara pemerintah dan Shakti…
The Periscope agreement.
Periscope perjanjian.
It's an open contract that allows them
Itu Sebuah buka kontrak Itu allows mereka
to use that program in any way they choose, for the next 10 years.
Ke gunakan itu program di apa pun cara Mereka choose, untuk berikutnya 10 tahun.
- Let me explain how it is possible. - Sir?
- Biarkan saya jelaskan bagaimana itu mungkin. - Pak?
Cut his mic and get him off the stage!
Potong dia mic Dan dapatkan dia mati stage!
- From 2021... - Sure, sir.
- Dari 2021... - Yakin, Pak.
the company has been--
perusahaan sudah sudah--
Hey!
Hei!
Really sorry, sir.
Benar-benar maaf, Pak.
You can't present this here.
Kamu bisa'T mempresentasikan ini sini.
What are you talking about?
Apa yang kamu Bicara tentang?
I am an invited guest here!
Saya Sebuah invited guest sini!
I decide what I'm going to talk about.
Saya putuskan apa saya akan bicara tentang.
You have no right to interrupt my speech!
Kamu punya tidak benar ke Interrupt saya speech!
- Please, sir... - Hey! Leave me!
- Tolong, Pak... - Hei! Pergi saya!
Are you trying to manhandle me?
Apa kamu Mencoba ke manhandle saya?
Hey, leave me!
Hei, pergi saya!
I really regret it now.
Saya benar-benar regret itu sekarang.
I was the one who pushed you to come to this event.
Saya satu siapa pushed kamu Ke datang ke ini acara.
It's not on you.
Itu Tidak di kamu.
It was my decision to come here and speak.
Itu saya decision Ke kemari dan bicara.
And look what happened!
Dan lihat apa yang terjadi!
You had promised me, you wouldn't create any controversy!
Kamu sudah promised saya, kamu tidak akan Create apa pun controversy!
Shut up!
Diam!
You have no right
Kamu punya tidak benar
to dictate what I should say!
Ke dictate apa Saya harus katakan!
- We just need two minutes of his time, please.
- Kita hanya perlu dua Menit dari dia waktu, tolong.
Hello? Hello?
Halo? Halo?
- Hello? - Yeah.
- Halo? - Ya.
- Yeah, Ma'am.
- Ya, Bu.
This is for a response. Daniel sir's response.
Ini Untuk sebuah tanggapan. Daniel Pak tanggapan.
- We just need two minutes. - This is for you.
- Kita hanya perlu dua menit. - ini Untuk kamu.
- Not me. - Is it possible?
- Tidak saya. - itu mungkin?
Hello?
Halo?
Two passengers.
Dua penumpang.
- Hey, see that guy over there? - Yeah.
- Hei, lihat itu pria atas sana? - Ya.
- Show me your hands. - Okay.
- Tunjukkan saya kamu tangan. - Oke.
- There you go!
- Sana kamu pergi!
Let's try.
Biarkan coba.
- This is your last prank. - Okay.
- ini Kamu lalu lelucon. - Oke.
- Rush, rush! - Let's try. Come.
- Rush, rush! - Biarkan coba. Datang.
Hey, come, come!
Hei, datang, datang!
Be quick!
Menjadi quick!
- Excuse me!
- Permisi saya!
- Way, please!
- Cara, tolong!
- Hey! - Hey! Who is this?!
- Hei! - Hei! Siapa ini?!
What! What are you doing?!
Apa! Apa yang kamu Melakukan?!
What's going on here?
Apa pergi di sini?
Come, come!
Datang, datang!
Who were those people? What's the problem?
Siapa itu orang? Apa masalah?
They just came from behind and they attacked him.
Mereka hanya datang dari di belakang Dan mereka diserang dia.
It's okay.
Itu Oke.
- Sorry, Ma'am! - Are you all right?
- Maaf, Bu! - apa kamu baiklah?
- It's just a prank for YouTube! - Fine.
- itu Hanya sebuah lelucon untuk YouTube! - Baik.
Your face will be our next thumbnail, sir.
Kamu wajah akan menjadi Kita berikutnya thumbnail, Pak.
Sorry!
Maaf!
Here.
Sini.
You alright?
Kamu baiklah?
Just a bit dizzy.
Hanya sebuah bit dizzy.
I think my sugar's low.
Saya pikir saya sugar's rendah.
Give me my medicine.
Beri saya saya obat.
Why did you drink so much yesterday?
Kenapa melakukan kamu minum Jadi banyak kemarin?
You are not allowed to drink, Danny.
Kamu tidak allowed Ke minum, Danny.
- Do you want some water? - No
- Lakukan kamu mau beberapa water? - Tidak
I'll just go to the washroom.
Saya akan Hanya pergi ke washroom.
I'll be fine.
Saya akan Menjadi baik.
Your attention, please.
Kamu perhatian, tolong.
This is the final boarding call for the flight to London.
Ini Terakhir boarding telepon Untuk penerbangan ke London.
We are now inviting all remaining passengers--
Kita Sekarang inviting semua Remaining penumpang--
Your attention, please.
Kamu perhatian, tolong.
This is the final boarding call for the flight to London Heathrow.
Ini Terakhir boarding telepon Untuk penerbangan ke London Heathrow.
This is the final boarding call...
Ini Terakhir boarding telepon...
Gate doors will close in approximately five minutes.
Gerbang pintu akan tutup Di approximately lima menit.
I need your help.
Saya perlu kamu tolong.
My husband is inside and it's final call for boarding.
Saya suami di dalam Dan itu terakhir telepon untuk boarding.
Could you please check on him?
Bisa kamu tolong periksa di dia?
In the bathroom? Come, let's check.
Di bathroom? Datang, biarkan periksa.
So, the passenger has taken the opposite exit...
Jadi, penumpang sudah diambil opposite keluar...
and he's going to the next terminal.
Dan dia pergi Ke berikutnya terminal.
Sir, that's not Daniel!
Pak, itu tidak Daniel!
That's not how Daniel walks.
Itu Tidak bagaimana Daniel jalan.
There's something wrong here.
Ada Sesuatu salah sini.
How is that possible?
Bagaimana itu mungkin?
He was supposed to board a flight to London!
Dia seharusnya ke naik Sebuah penerbangan ke London!
It is possible, sir.
Itu mungkin, Pak.
Passenger is travelling to his home country.
Penumpang travelling Ke dia rumah negara.
We have his web check-in details for that flight.
Kita sudah Dia web periksa-di details Untuk itu penerbangan.
No luggage.
Tidak luggage.
Put the boarding pass.
Taruh boarding pass.
He has already boarded the flight.
Dia sudah sudah naik penerbangan.
Sir, something's wrong here.
Pak, sesuatu salah sini.
Daniel will never go to his home country!
Daniel akan tidak pernah pergi Ke dia rumah negara!
His life is under threat there!
Dia hidup bawah ancaman sana!
It's not Danny who travelled.
Itu Tidak Danny siapa bepergian.
Sir… one second.
Pak… sebentar.
How exactly is this woman related to him?
Bagaimana tepat ini wanita Related ke dia?
Abdul, she is Daniel's wife.
Abdul, dia Daniel istri.
I don't think they're legally married, sir.
Saya jangan pikir mereka Legally menikah, Pak.
Check his passport, sir.
Periksa dia paspor, Pak.
His spouse's name is listed as Lathika.
Dia spouse's nama daftar sebagai Lathika.
Sir, I think he must've travelled without telling her.
Pak, Saya pikir dia pasti sudah bepergian Tanpa beri tahu dia.
Sir, what's going on here?
Pak, apa pergi di sini?
I want to report this to the police.
Saya ingin Laporan ini Ke polisi.
I want to know where Daniel is!
Saya ingin tahu di mana Daniel!
Why doesn't anyone understand this?
Kenapa tidak siapa pun Mengerti ini?
Don't panic like this, Ayesha.
Jangan Panik suka ini, Ayesha.
This is not under my authority.
Ini Tidak bawah saya authority.
Let the flight land in Kochi.
Biarkan penerbangan mendarat di Kochi.
I have sources there.
Saya sudah Sources sana.
Alright?
Baiklah?
XV524 FRA to Kochi...
XV524 FRA ke Kochi...
Arrival is scheduled at 5:30 PM.
Kedatangan scheduled di 5:30 PM.
The flight is on time, sir. Any issue?
Penerbangan di waktu, Pak. Apa pun masalah?
The former scientific advisor of NHM, Daniel,
Former ilmiah penasihat Dari NHM, Daniel,
is arriving on that flight.
arriving di situ penerbangan.
Once the flight lands,
Sekali penerbangan mendarat,
send me his immigration photo and entry stamp.
Kirim saya dia imigrasi foto Dan masuk stamp.
Sure, sir.
Yakin, Pak.
Thank you, Sreeni.
Terima kasih, Sreeni.
These were the kids who pulled that prank on him.
Ini anak-anak siapa tarik Itu lelucon di dia.
It was after this that Danny started feeling weak.
Itu setelah ini itu Danny mulai feeling weak.
That's why I'm saying this with certainty,
Itu Kenapa saya katakan ini Dengan certainty,
Danny's life is in danger!
Danny hidup di bahaya!
Why didn't you complain immediately?
Kenapa tidak kamu Complain segera?
Those kids ran out immediately.
Itu anak-anak ran keluar segera.
The guy who shot the video said it was a prank
Pria siapa tembakan video Berkata itu sebuah lelucon
and apologised to Danny.
Dan apologised ke Danny.
But they've sprayed something on him.
Tapi they've sprayed Sesuatu di dia.
I'm sure about it!
Saya Yakin tentang itu!
Send this jacket to the lab immediately and get a forensic report on it.
Kirim ini jacket ke lab segera Dan dapatkan sebuah forensic laporan di situ.
It's urgent.
Itu Urgent.
Ayesha, your phone?
Ayesha, teleponmu?
This is a photo of two people who seemed suspicious at the airport today.
Ini sebuah Foto dari dua orang siapa tampak Suspicious di bandara hari ini.
Get their details from the Malayali association.
Dapatkan mereka details Dari Malayali association.
Sure, sir.
Yakin, Pak.
Question them through the consulate, without involving the local police.
Pertanyaan mereka melalui consulate, Tanpa involving local polisi.
- Alright? - Alright.
- Baiklah? - Baiklah.
Come, Ayesha.
Datang, Ayesha.
Ayesha, just be seated here. I'll be right back.
Ayesha, hanya menjadi kursi sini. Saya akan Menjadi benar kembali.
Sir, Daniel didn't tweet anything
Pak, Daniel tidak cuitan apa pun
during the last three days of the event.
Selama lalu tiga hari Dari acara.
This is all fabricated!
Ini Semua fabricated!
This is JPS's official tweet.
Ini JPS's resmi cuitan.
Do you think they'd repost it if it wasn't verified?
Lakukan kamu pikir they'd repost itu Jika itu tidak verified?
As far as I know, Daniel's health was normal until we arrived here.
Sebagai jauh sebagai Saya tahu, Daniel kesehatan normal sampai kita tiba sini.
I can show you his last medical reports.
Saya bisa tunjukkan kamu Dia lalu medis laporan.
Didn't he mention that to you, sir?
Tidak Dia mention itu ke kamu, Pak?
Sreeni...
Sreeni...
A Shakti Group ambulance is waiting here, sir.
Sebuah Shakti Group ambulans tunggu sini, Pak.
There's a medical emergency reported
Ada Sebuah medis darurat laporan
under the same passenger name, Daniel James.
Bawah sama penumpang nama, Daniel James.
He'll be taken straight from the flight to the ambulance.
He'll menjadi diambil straight dari penerbangan Ke ambulans.
Sreeni... I told you, right?
Sreeni... Sudah saya bilang, Benar?
At any risk,
Di apa pun risiko,
I need a picture of Daniel when he clears immigration!
Saya perlu sebuah picture dari Daniel Kapan dia jelas imigrasi!
They were two guys, Vicky and Yusuf.
Mereka dua teman-teman, Vicky dan Yusuf.
Neither of you knew these guys before?
Neither dari kamu Tahu ini teman-teman sebelum?
No, sir.
Tidak, Pak.
We just went there to be volunteers.
Kita hanya pergi sana Ke menjadi volunteers.
And the videos were uploaded?
Dan video diunggah?
They said all the videos would be uploaded together.
Mereka berkata semua video Akan menjadi diunggah bersama.
Who asked you to do such a prank inside the airport?
Siapa bertanya kamu ke lakukan seperti itu Sebuah lelucon di dalam bandara?
It was Vicky's suggestion.
Itu Vicky's suggestion.
And that sir was also at the event, right?
Dan itu Pak juga Di acara, benar?
So we didn't think it would be a problem.
Jadi kita tidak pikir Itu akan menjadi sebuah masalah.
Like always,
Suka selalu,
we took the moisturising lotion from them.
Kita mengambil moisturising losion Dari mereka.
But the lotion they gave that time…
Tapi losion mereka memberi Itu waktu…
It seemed a bit different.
Itu tampak sebuah bit berbeda.
A while after I applied it on my hands,
Sebuah saat setelah Saya applied itu Di saya tangan,
I felt a burning sensation.
Saya felt sebuah burning sensation.
Extremely sorry, sir.
Extremely maaf, Pak.
It was a direct order from the ministry.
Itu sebuah direct perintah Dari ministry.
Immigration clearance was bypassed,
Imigrasi izin bypassed,
and Daniel has been moved to Shakti Institute of Medical Science.
Dan Daniel sudah sudah pindah ke Shakti Institute dari Medis Science.
I couldn't verify his passport, sir.
Saya tidak bisa verify Dia paspor, Pak.
Let's head to the airport.
Biarkan kepala ke bandara.
Your luggage must've been offloaded there.
Kamu luggage pasti sudah sudah Offloaded sana.
By the time you collect it, I'll find Danny.
Oleh waktu kamu collect itu, Saya akan Temukan Danny.
Could you please tell me where this group of men are heading?
Bisa kamu tolong beri tahu saya di mana Ini grup dari pria kepala?
Hey, what's in that letter?
Hei, apa di situ surat?
Since they have a performance the next day,
Sejak mereka punya sebuah performance hari berikutnya,
it's a permission letter exempting the musical instruments from X-ray scanning.
itu Sebuah izin surat exempting Musical instruments dari X-ray scanning.
But how is that even possible?
Tapi bagaimana itu bahkan mungkin?
Fine-tuned musical instruments are exempt from scanning.
Baik-tuned musical instruments exempt dari scanning.
That's the arriving country's headache.
Itu arriving negara headache.
We already screened them when they arrived here.
Kita sudah layar mereka Kapan mereka tiba sini.
Such equipment is exempted during departure.
Seperti itu equipment exempted Selama keberangkatan.
They should have travelled from terminal C.
Mereka harus punya bepergian Dari terminal C.
Why did they take this entry?
Kenapa melakukan mereka ambil ini masuk?
Abdul, who was that flight chartered for?
Abdul, siapa itu penerbangan Chartered untuk?
It was scheduled by Shakti Corporation.
Itu scheduled oleh Shakti Perusahaan.
Departure time was 7:15 in the evening.
Keberangkatan waktu 7:15 Di sore.
Destination?
Destination?
Kochi Marine Base Airport.
Kochi Marine Basis Bandara.
Sir, it's confirmed in the report.
Pak, itu dikonfirmasi di laporan.
A chemical called VX nerve agent was used.
Sebuah kimia menelepon VX saraf agent digunakan.
The symptoms match the girls' statements.
Symptoms cocok gadis' pernyataan.
Ayesha, what was the last medicine Daniel took?
Ayesha, apa lalu Obat Daniel mengambil?
Err...
Err...
Ayesha, Danny was poisoned.
Ayesha, Danny diracuni.
As per my assumption, he has been kidnapped in a private carrier.
Sebagai per saya assumption, dia sudah sudah Kidnapped di sebuah pribadi carrier.
But he won't die
Tapi dia tidak akan mati
because he sensed the poisoning beforehand!
Karena dia sensed poisoning beforehand!
Sir, this is the team.
Pak, ini tim.
The team leader is Vignesh, alias Vicky.
Tim pemimpin Vignesh, Alias Vicky.
SP, STF. 2014 batch.
SP, STF. 2014 Angkatan.
Ahmed Yusuf alias Yusuf,
Ahmed Yusuf alias Yusuf,
DySP, STF.
DySP, STF.
Expert in counter-surveillance and interrogation, 2011 batch.
Expert di counter-pengawasan Dan interrogation, 2011 angkatan.
VX, also known as Novichok, was developed
VX, juga diketahui sebagai Novichok, developed
at the DRW lab in Avadi.
Di DRW lab di Avadi.
Sai was in charge of monitoring its levels.
Sai di tuduhan Dari pemantauan itu levels.
They must have run trials there to test
Mereka harus punya lari trials Sana ke test
if it could be used in moisturising lotion packets.
Jika itu bisa menjadi digunakan Di moisturising losion packets.
Tie his legs!
Tie dia legs!
Sir! Sir! Sir!
Pak! Pak! Pak!
Sir, Daniel has retrieved his Twitter account.
Pak, Daniel sudah retrieved Dia Twitter account.
VIMATHAN [Dissident]
Vimathan [Pembangkang]
The post thanking you was taken down five minutes ago.
Kiriman terima kasih kamu Diambil turun lima menit lalu.
If he is alive right now,
Jika dia hidup sekarang juga,
he will respond soon!
Dia akan tanggapi segera!
[VIMATHAN HAS ENDED HIS EXILE]
[Vimathan HAS Ended HIS Exile]
I don't want any speculations.
Saya tidak mau Apa pun speculations.
Daniel James has been working as a lecturer in the U.K. all this time.
Daniel James sudah sudah bekerja Sebagai sebuah lecturer di U.K. Semua ini waktu.
But ever since he left,
Tapi pernah sejak dia pergi,
his health has been continuously deteriorating.
Dia kesehatan sudah sudah Terus-menerus deteriorating.
So...
Jadi...
it's the government's responsibility
itu pemerintah tanggung jawab
to ensure he receives the medical treatment he deserves.
Ke pastikan dia menerima medis treatment dia deserves.
So I'm just facilitating that.
Jadi saya hanya facilitating itu.
Hello, doc...
Halo, doc...
If the patient isn't brought to the hospital soon,
Jika pasien tidak membawa Ke rumah sakit segera,
things could get complicated.
Hal-hal bisa dapatkan complicated.
I understand.
Saya mengerti.
I understand your concern.
Saya mengerti kamu concern.
My team will get Daniel here as quickly as possible.
Saya tim akan dapatkan Daniel sini Sebagai cepat sebagai mungkin.
- So, you be prepared... - Okay.
- Jadi, kamu menjadi prepared... - Oke.
- And let's hope for the best. - Alright.
- Dan biarkan hope untuk best. - Baiklah.
Where are they?
Di mana mereka?
They are in the board room, sir.
Mereka Di naik ruangan, Pak.
How many times have I told you
Bagaimana banyak waktu punya sudah saya bilang
not to underestimate him!
Tidak ke underestimate dia!
He is a trained...
Dia Sebuah trained...
Sir, our execution hasn't slipped anywhere.
Pak, kita execution belum Slipped anywhere.
The amount of chemical we used was perfect.
Amount dari kimia Kita digunakan sempurna.
- Even then-- - Did I ask for an explanation?
- Bahkan lalu-- - Melakukan Saya tanya untuk sebuah explanation?
Wherever he is,
Di mana pun dia,
find me Daniel right now!
Temukan saya Daniel sekarang juga!
Or else, this leave period of yours...
Atau lain, Ini pergi period dari milikmu...
I will turn it into a dismissal order!
Saya akan Putar itu ke dalam sebuah dismissal perintah!
Is that clear?
Itu jelas?
Daniel doesn't have the strength to survive that fall.
Daniel tidak punya strength ke bertahan itu jatuh.
There's no way he's still alive.
Ada tidak mungkin dia Masih hidup.
- Then find me his body! - Sir...
- Lalu temukan saya dia tubuh! - Pak...
Daniel's wife is causing a scene, insisting on seeing him.
Daniel istri causing sebuah adegan, Insisting di lihat dia.
You need to come speak to her,
Kamu harus datang bicara ke dia,
or she won't stop.
Atau dia tidak akan berhenti.
Why won't you let me see my husband?
Kenapa tidak akan kamu biarkan saya Lihat saya suami?
Daniel, who's inside... I'm his partner.
Daniel, siapa di dalam... Saya Dia partner.
I have every right to see him.
Saya sudah Setiap benar ke lihat dia.
Ma'am, strictly no visitors.
Bu, ketat tidak visitors.
Those are the doctor's orders.
Itu dokter perintah.
- Hey, stop it! - Sir, my name is Ayesha Iqbal.
- Hei, berhenti itu! - Pak, nama saya Ayesha Iqbal.
I am Daniel's wife.
Saya Daniel istri.
He was supposed to return with me,
Dia seharusnya ke Return dengan saya,
but you had him kidnapped and brought here!
Tapi kamu sudah dia kidnapped Dan membawa sini!
I need to see him!
Saya harus Lihat dia!
Listen, Madam. I've just come from checking on Daniel's condition.
Dengar, Bu. saya sudah Hanya datang dari Periksa di Daniel condition.
Visitors will only be allowed once the doctors give permission.
Visitors akan hanya menjadi allowed Sekali dokter beri izin.
This is a hospital.
Ini sebuah Rumah sakit.
We have to follow the rules.
Kita harus ikuti rules.
I'm not just any visitor.
Saya tidak Hanya apa pun visitor.
I'm his wife!
Saya Dia istri!
Sorry, I don't understand.
Maaf, Saya jangan mengerti.
How exactly is Daniel your husband?
Bagaimana tepat Daniel Kamu suami?
Are you legally married to him?
Apa kamu Legally menikah ke dia?
To prove what you're saying...
Ke buktikan apa kamu katakan...
Is there any legal relationship between you and Daniel?
Sana apa pun hukum relationship Antara kamu dan Daniel?
We've been living together for a while now.
Kita sudah Sudah hidup bersama sebentar Sekarang.
- Isn't that proof enough? - That might work in your country!
- tidak Itu proof cukup? - Itu mungkin kerja di kamu negara!
The Daniel I know has only been married once.
Daniel Saya tahu Sudah hanya sudah menikah sekali.
It might have been a failed marriage,
Itu mungkin punya sudah Sebuah failed marriage,
but that woman...
Tapi itu wanita...
is right here.
di sini.
Why are you more concerned than she is?
Kenapa apa kamu lebih khawatir Daripada dia?
So, as far as I and this hospital management are concerned,
Jadi, sebagai jauh sebagai Saya dan ini rumah sakit Management khawatir,
you're nothing more than an ordinary visitor.
kamu Tidak ada lebih daripada Sebuah biasa visitor.
Is that clear?
Itu jelas?
Ayesha, get into the car.
Ayesha, dapatkan ke dalam mobil.
Madam, I'm glad I could meet you here,
Bu, saya glad Saya bisa temui kamu sini,
but you don't know the situation Daniel is in.
Tapi kamu jangan tahu situasi Daniel di.
At least, can you take this seriously?
Setidaknya, bisakah kamu Ambil ini seriously?
Daniel has been poisoned.
Daniel sudah sudah diracuni.
Our priority should be to get him out of here immediately.
Kita priority harus menjadi ke dapatkan dia Keluar dari sini segera.
Ayesha...
Ayesha...
Get in.
Dapatkan di.
If we leave, they'll kill Daniel!
Jika kita pergi, mereka akan Bunuh Daniel!
I'm certain of it!
Saya Tertentu dari itu!
But who told you Danny is even in there?
Tapi siapa memberi tahu kamu Danny bahkan di sana?
The hospital only has his name on the register.
Rumah sakit hanya sudah Dia nama di register.
He's not inside.
Dia Tidak di dalam.
There's no point shouting here.
Ada Tidak poin berteriak sini.
Just get in, Ayesha.
Hanya dapatkan di, Ayesha.
Danny is safe.
Danny aman.
Nothing's going to happen to him.
Tidak ada akan terjadi ke dia.
How do you know that?
Bagaimana lakukan kamu tahu itu?
I can't tell you that right now.
Saya tidak bisa beri tahu kamu itu sekarang juga.
Wear your seat belt.
Wear kamu kursi belt.
Come. I want you to meet somebody.
Datang. Saya ingin kamu Ke temui seseorang.
Give me your ID.
Beri saya kamu ID.
How is she now, Chechi?
Bagaimana dia sekarang, Chechi?
She's started eating again.
Dia Mulai eating lagi.
She's undergoing a scan now.
Dia Undergoing sebuah scan sekarang.
Chechi, can you please come inside?
Chechi, bisakah kamu tolong Datang di dalam?
We've got a date for next Thursday.
Kita sudah Mendapat sebuah tanggal Untuk berikutnya Thursday.
Are you scared to appear in court, dear?
Apa kamu Scared Ke appear di pengadilan, sayang?
[Lathika] Do you recognise that girl, Ayesha?
[Lathika] apa kamu mengenali Itu gadis, Ayesha?
- [Ayesha] No. - [Lathika] She is Athira,
- [Ayesha] Tidak. - [Lathika] dia Athira,
a 11th standard student.
Sebuah 11th standard mahasiswa.
A victim of Shakti's free laptop scheme.
Sebuah korban dari Shakti bebas laptop skema.
It was at my request, for her sake,
Itu di saya permintaan, Untuk dia sake,
that Daniel shot that vlog.
Itu Daniel tembakan itu vlog.
Making sure she didn't make it to court
Membuat yakin dia tidak buat itu ke pengadilan
was vital for the Shakti Group.
vital untuk Shakti Group.
Luckily, she survived.
Untungnya, dia survived.
For the next hearing, we need her in court to give her statement.
Untuk berikutnya dengar, kita perlu dia Di pengadilan ke beri dia pernyataan.
That's what Daniel needs.
Itu Apa Daniel perlu.
Only a victim's testimony...
Hanya sebuah korban testimony...
can win us this case.
Bisa menang kita ini kasus.
If your office can't even handle a single document safely,
Jika kamu kantor tidak bisa bahkan handle Sebuah satu dokumen safely,
I think you should shut this company down!
Saya pikir kamu harus Diam ini perusahaan turun!
That's my problem, Dad.
Itu Saya masalah, Ayah.
That's not why I got the summons, is it?
Itu Tidak kenapa Saya mendapat summons, itu?
Hey, I've got so many cases against me.
Hei, saya sudah mendapat jadi banyak kasus Terhadap saya.
Do I show up for every hearing?
Lakukan Saya tunjukkan atas untuk setiap dengar?
I told you, son...
Sudah saya bilang, Anak laki-laki...
let's shift the dates!
Biarkan giliran tanggal!
I'm not like you, Dad.
Saya tidak Suka kamu, Ayah.
I don't play dirty games like switching judges the moment I get a summons!
Saya jangan main dirty games suka switching Hakim moment Saya dapatkan sebuah summons!
If Daniel is the reason this reached court,
Jika Daniel alasan Ini reached pengadilan,
you should've dealt with him!
kamu harus'Ve dealt dengan dia!
I should've dealt with him!
Saya seharusnya sudah dealt dengan dia!
Hey, he is a...
Hei, dia sebuah...
popular figure!
Popular figure!
No matter what we do to him,
Tidak urusan apa kita lakukan ke dia,
people will blame me!
Orang akan blame saya!
How many people am I answerable to?
Bagaimana banyak orang Saya answerable ke?
And look where we are now.
Dan lihat di mana kita sekarang.
I told you again and again this foolish plan would never work!
Sudah saya bilang Lagi dan lagi Ini foolish rencana akan tidak pernah kerja!
But you still wanted to bring him back and prove he'd joined your side!
Tapi kamu masih ingin untuk membawa dia kembali Dan buktikan he'd joined kamu sisi!
Fake treatment, transplant, killing.
Fake treatment, transplantasi, bunuh.
It's all fallen apart now, hasn't it?
Itu Semua fallen terpisah sekarang, belum Itu?
Dad...
Ayah...
you should understand one thing!
kamu harus Mengerti satu hal!
Throughout your life,
Throughout kamu hidup,
you've never had a clean image in politics!
kamu sudah Tidak pernah sudah Sebuah clean image di politics!
Hey, you're using my money to run this company!
Hei, kamu menggunakan saya uang Ke lari ini perusahaan!
But I'm running the damn show here!
Tapi saya berjalan sial tunjukkan sini!
No one's going to build statues for you or name roads after you.
Tidak ada orang'S akan bangun statues untuk kamu Atau nama jalan setelah kamu.
No matter how much money you burn on it,
Tidak urusan bagaimana banyak uang Kamu burn di situ,
you're not going to earn it!
kamu Tidak akan earn itu!
Can you please tell me where Danny is right now?
Bisakah kamu Tolong beri tahu saya Di mana Danny sekarang juga?
Didn't I tell you? He is safe.
Tidak Saya beri tahu kamu? Dia Aman.
That's all I know.
Itu Semua Saya tahu.
There's somebody who's helping him.
Ada Seseorang Siapa tolong dia.
I came to the hospital
Saya datang ke rumah sakit
just to avoid any suspicion.
Hanya ke avoid apa pun suspicion.
They are ruthless criminals.
Mereka Ruthless penjahat.
This used to be Daniel's study.
Ini digunakan ke menjadi Daniel belajar.
When we separated,
Kapan kita separated,
I got this house.
Saya mendapat ini rumah.
You can freshen up here.
Kamu bisa Freshen atas sini.
Take some rest.
Ambil beberapa rest.
Nothing's going to happen...
Tidak ada akan terjadi...
to the Daniel I know.
Ke Daniel Saya tahu.
I'll get an update soon.
Saya akan Dapatkan sebuah pembaruan segera.
Listen, you guys!
Dengar, kamu teman-teman!
We're really running out of time!
Kita Benar-benar berjalan keluar dari waktu!
Go get me the phone.
Pergi dapatkan saya telepon.
Everything Daniel did at the summit, everyone he met,
Semuanya Daniel melakukan di konferensi, semua orang dia bertemu,
the video he played at the event, each and everything!
video dia main di acara, Masing-masing dan semuanya!
I want it on the screen... now!
Saya ingin itu di layar... Sekarang!
I don't want a damn vlogger to be the end of Shakti!
Saya tidak mau Sebuah sial vlogger Ke menjadi akhir dari Shakti!
What's happening? Get to work!
Apa terjadi? Dapatkan ke kerja!
Listen, Dibakar... Don't panic.
Dengar, Dibakar... jangan Panik.
Let's work from reverse. You have his video, right?
Biarkan kerja dari reverse. Kamu punya dia video, benar?
Get me that first!
Dapatkan saya itu pertama!
Yeah.
Ya.
This is the secret behind that single click.
Ini Rahasia Di belakang itu satu klik.
Freeze there!
Freeze sana!
Zoom the document.
Zoom dokumen.
This is the original document with my signature!
Ini Original dokumen Dengan saya tanda tangan!
Highly classified!
Highly rahasia!
A legal agreement known only to Shakti Group and the Government.
Sebuah hukum perjanjian diketahui hanya Ke Shakti Group dan Pemerintah.
How did he get it?
Bagaimana melakukan dia dapatkan itu?
How the hell did Daniel get it??
Bagaimana hell melakukan Daniel dapatkan itu??
It's gone from here.
Itu Pergi dari sini.
Throw the names of everyone with access to this document up on the screen.
Throw nama dari semua orang dengan akses Ke ini dokumen atas di layar.
Throw it!
Throw itu!
On your screen, sir.
Di kamu layar, Pak.
Scroll down.
Scroll turun.
Stop.
Berhenti.
Did Michael have access to it?
Melakukan Michael punya akses ke itu?
Yes, sir. Michael was handling the program alterations.
Ya, Pak. Michael handling program alterations.
So where is Michael now?
Jadi di mana Michael sekarang?
Where is he?
Di mana dia?
Michael hasn't been to the office for the past two weeks.
Michael belum sudah ke kantor selama Dua minggu.
After Jyothi died, his colleagues say...
Setelah Jyothi meninggal, Dia colleagues katakan...
that he's moved back to his wife's place in Bangalore.
Itu dia pindah kembali Ke dia istri tempat di Bangalore.
Dibakar, just think about it.
Dibakar, hanya pikir tentang itu.
Even after getting hold of such an exclusive document,
Bahkan setelah mendapatkan pegang Dari seperti itu sebuah exclusive dokumen,
why hasn't Daniel made a vlog about it yet?
Kenapa belum Daniel membuat Sebuah vlog tentang itu belum?
Why wait for our summit to reveal it?
Kenapa tunggu untuk kita konferensi Ke reveal itu?
And if it was Michael who gave it to Daniel,
Dan jika itu Michael Siapa memberi itu ke Daniel,
Micheal would never send it by email.
Micheal akan Tidak pernah kirim itu oleh email.
He's not that stupid!
Dia Tidak itu stupid!
Hello sir, This is Ayesha.
Halo Pak, ini Ayesha.
Danny has booked a ticket to Faraha for somebody named Michael.
Danny sudah booked sebuah tiket ke Faraha Untuk seseorang named Michael.
Send that ticket to me. I'll check.
Kirim itu tiket ke saya. Saya akan Periksa.
Michael met Daniel in person.
Michael bertemu Daniel di orang.
And it happened during our event.
Dan itu terjadi Selama kita acara.
Shortlist Bangalore-Faraha flight timings.
Shortlist Bangalore-Faraha Penerbangan timings.
Get all the visual data from our arrival kiosks
Dapatkan semua visual data Dari kita kedatangan kiosks
on the screen now, please.
Di layar sekarang, tolong.
Sir...
Pak...
Yes. Play.
Ya. Main.
Not this, not this. Forward.
Tidak ini, tidak ini. Maju.
Forward, forward.
Maju, maju.
Move!
Bergerak!
Apply face match using Michael's facial attributes.
Apply wajah cocok Menggunakan Michael facial attributes.
When did he get there?
Kapan melakukan dia dapatkan sana?
Sir, final day of the event.
Pak, terakhir hari dari acara.
Morning 2:35 AM arrival time.
Pagi 2:35 AM kedatangan waktu.
He crossed the arrival gate at 5:10 AM.
Dia melewati kedatangan gerbang Di 5:10 AM.
The same day Daniel gave his presentation, right?
Hari yang sama Daniel memberi Dia presentation, benar?
Yes, sir.
Ya, Pak.
Do you know this Michael, Ayesha?
Lakukan kamu tahu ini Michael, Ayesha?
No way, sir!
Tidak mungkin, Pak!
Danny usually tells me everything,
Danny usually beri tahu saya semuanya,
but he has never mentioned anyone by that name.
Tapi dia sudah tidak pernah mentioned Siapa pun oleh itu nama.
Michael arrived the same day Daniel gave his talk.
Michael tiba hari yang sama Daniel memberi dia bicara.
Moreover, he returned the same day.
Moreover, Dia returned hari yang sama.
That means Michael spent only about 6 hours in Faraha.
Itu berarti Michael spent Hanya tentang 6 jam di Faraha.
Ayesha, could you recollect
Ayesha, bisa kamu recollect
anything unusual from Danny that day?
Apa pun tidak biasa Dari Danny itu hari?
Sir, he went out for a walk early in the morning.
Pak, dia pergi keluar untuk sebuah jalan Early di pagi.
Let me step out for a walk.
Biarkan saya langkah keluar untuk sebuah jalan.
It's suffocating in here.
Itu Suffocating di sini.
Daniel doesn't usually go for walks.
Daniel tidak usually pergi untuk jalan.
Let me check.
Biarkan saya periksa.
Vignesh! You were there, right?
Vignesh! Kamu sana, benar?
And yet, none of you noticed him leave?
Dan belum, none dari kamu Noticed dia pergi?
You should've just followed him!
Kamu harus'Ve hanya ikuti dia!
We were sticking to our plan.
Kita sticking ke kita rencana.
We didn't have instructions to follow Daniel.
Kita tidak punya instruksi Ke ikuti Daniel.
Is it, Vignesh?
Itu, Vignesh?
Are you incapable of making your own decisions?
Apa kamu Incapable Dari membuat kamu sendiri decisions?
All grown up now,
Semua grown atas sekarang,
aren't you?
tidak Kamu?
Yeah, the passenger took a cab from the airport.
Ya, penumpang mengambil sebuah cab Dari bandara.
It then crossed Highway 38,
Itu lalu melewati Highway 38,
entered Omar Syed avenue,
Entered Omar Syed avenue,
and then finally it stopped at The Paul, 3rd street.
Dan lalu akhirnya Itu stopped di Paul, 3rd street.
Could you please let me know
Bisa kamu tolong biarkan saya tahu
if a person wearing a cap has entered the location further?
Jika sebuah orang wearing sebuah cap Sudah entered lokasi further?
Yeah, that's true.
Ya, itu benar.
As per my assumption,
Sebagai per saya assumption,
Daniel met Michael somewhere outside the resort.
Daniel bertemu Michael Somewhere di luar resort.
20 minutes...
20 Menit...
Daniel spent 20 minutes with Michael.
Daniel spent 20 menit dengan Michael.
Michael must have handed over our document to Daniel
Michael harus punya tangan atas Kita dokumen ke Daniel
within that time.
Dalam itu waktu.
This is an agreement signed by DRW and Shakti Group in 2021.
Ini Sebuah perjanjian ditandatangani oleh DRW dan Shakti Group di 2021.
It is the only document that proves
Itu hanya dokumen itu buktikan
they have been using Periscope to spy on civilians.
Mereka punya sudah menggunakan Periscope ke spy di warga sipil.
Where did you get it from?
Di mana melakukan kamu dapatkan itu dari?
When Periscope was handed over to Shakti,
Kapan Periscope tangan atas Ke Shakti,
I was the person responsible.
Saya orang bertanggung jawab.
Every year, when the program is updated,
Setiap tahun, Kapan program updated,
I'm required to verify this document.
Saya Diperlukan ke verify Ini dokumen.
I need you to present this at the summit for me, Danny sir.
Saya perlu kamu untuk mempresentasikan ini Di konferensi untuk saya, Pak Danny.
Why should I trust you?
Kenapa harus Saya percaya kamu?
Sir, I told you, right?
Pak, sudah saya bilang, benar?
I need redemption.
Saya perlu redemption.
Sympathy for your dead girlfriend!
Sympathy untuk kamu mati girlfriend!
And yet you don't have the nerve to expose any of this yourself!
Dan belum kamu jangan punya saraf Ke expose apa pun dari ini yourself!
I pity you, Michael.
Saya pity kamu, Michael.
You should be the one disclosing this, not me.
Kamu harus Menjadi satu Disclosing ini, tidak saya.
Jyothi wanted to be an approver in court against Shakti Group.
Jyothi ingin ke menjadi sebuah approver Di pengadilan terhadap Shakti Group.
It's difficult for me, sir.
Itu Sulit untuk saya, Pak.
With the non-disclosure agreements I've already signed...
Dengan non-disclosure perjanjian Saya sudah Sudah ditandatangani...
the contracts...
kontrak...
my family, my child...
Saya keluarga, saya anak...
Wasn't Jyothi your family as well?
Tidak Jyothi kamu keluarga sebagai baiklah?
Even if I'm the one who exposes this,
Bahkan jika saya satu siapa Exposes ini,
you'll still be in danger.
kamu akan Masih menjadi di bahaya.
But I'll know it
Tapi saya akan tahu itu
before you do.
Sebelum kamu lakukan.
You will get a call from this number.
Kamu akan dapatkan sebuah telepon Dari ini nomor.
Follow those instructions.
Ikuti itu instruksi.
I'm not saying this to provoke you.
Saya tidak Katakan ini Ke provoke kamu.
But you deserve to know.
Tapi kamu deserve ke tahu.
Jyothi didn't just die of natural causes.
Jyothi tidak hanya mati Dari natural causes.
To silence her once and for all,
Ke diam dia sekali dan untuk semua,
they murdered her!
Mereka murdered dia!
[Raghu] Michael got here on the day of Daniel's talk.
[Raghu] Michael mendapat sini Di hari dari Daniel bicara.
And he went back the same day.
Dan dia pergi kembali hari yang sama.
That...!
Itu...!
That is the lead we're looking for!
Itu pimpin kita Lihat untuk!
Michael Devassy.
Michael Devassy.
Find out where he is.
Temukan keluar di mana dia.
You find Michael, you get Daniel!
Kamu temukan Michael, Kamu dapatkan Daniel!
That's it!
Itu Itu!
- Dibakar. - Sir?
- Dibakar. - Pak?
How long did it take me to crack this?
Bagaimana lama melakukan itu ambil saya Ke crack ini?
Sir, almost 23 minutes.
Pak, hampir 23 menit.
23 minutes...
23 Menit...
The time I took to track and find someone.
Waktu Saya mengambil Ke lacak dan temukan seseorang.
That's more than enough.
Itu Lebih daripada cukup.
These are the possible location coordinates
Ini mungkin Lokasi coordinates
where Daniel might've landed, judging by his fall.
Di mana Daniel might've mendarat, Judging oleh dia jatuh.
It's close to Mangalore coastline.
Itu Tutup ke Mangalore coastline.
Unbelievable!
Unbelievable!
So he waited precisely until he crossed the border?
Jadi dia tunggu precisely Sampai dia melewati border?
Sir, we were almost 30 minutes away from landing.
Pak, kita hampir 30 Menit pergi dari pendaratan.
He must have calculated the airspace.
Dia harus punya calculated airspace.
But that fall...
Tapi itu jatuh...
he'd never survive that.
He'd tidak pernah bertahan itu.
Hey, go on.
Hei, pergi di.
Dad!
Ayah!
Vimathan's... Err...
Vimathan... Err...
Which IP address was Daniel's tweet posted from?
Yang IP address Daniel cuitan kiriman dari?
That's what struck me as strange.
Itu Apa struck saya sebagai strange.
The tweet was posted from Delhi.
Cuitan kiriman dari Delhi.
From Daniel's old apartment in Defence Colony.
Dari Daniel lama apartemen Di Pertahanan Colony.
He jumps into Mangalore and tweets from Delhi?
Dia jumps ke dalam Mangalore Dan cuitan dari Delhi?
Sir, it could be an automated reply.
Pak, itu bisa menjadi Sebuah automated balasan.
How else is that possible, sir?
Bagaimana lain itu mungkin, Pak?
Someone is helping him!
Seseorang tolong dia!
Give me your hand!
Beri saya kamu tangan!
English?
English?
Hindi?
Hindi?
Marathi?
Marathi?
Kannada, Kannada!
Kannada, Kannada!
[in Kannada] Which place is this?
[Di Kannada] Yang tempat ini?
Mangalore.
Mangalore.
Who are you, sir?
Siapa kamu, Pak?
Sir... Who are you, sir?
Pak... siapa kamu, Pak?
What are you doing?
Apa yang kamu Melakukan?
Who are you?
Siapa kamu?
Sir... Are you a terrorist or with the police?
Pak... apa kamu Sebuah teroris Atau dengan polisi?
Soldier!
Tentara!
Give me the radio.
Beri saya radio.
What if someone Daniel deeply trusts
Apa jika seseorang Daniel deeply percaya
tweeted on his behalf?
Cuitan di dia behalf?
- Yusuf. - Sir?
- Yusuf. - Pak?
Who maintains Daniel's Delhi apartment?
Siapa maintains Daniel Delhi apartemen?
A colonel who was with Daniel at the DTA,
Sebuah Kolonel siapa dengan Daniel di DTA,
Colonel Rahim Nayik.
Kolonel Rahim Nayik.
Retired.
Retired.
He's been bedridden for the past few years.
Dia Sudah bedridden selama Sedikit tahun.
Rahim Sahib.
Rahim Tuan.
Rahim Sir once taught me signal communication.
Rahim Pak sekali taught saya Signal communication.
We checked the colonel's call records.
Kita periksa Kolonel telepon rekam.
There's no suspicious behaviour.
Ada Tidak suspicious behaviour.
No new calls apart from his regular contacts in the past few days.
Tidak baru telepon terpisah dari Dia regular kontak di masa lalu sedikit hari.
You guys! That's because they're not using the modern way of communication!
Kamu teman-teman! itu Karena mereka tidak menggunakan modern cara dari communication!
Both of them are old Signal Corps officers.
Keduanya dari mereka Lama Signal Corps petugas.
Long before today's internet or social media even existed,
Lama sebelum hari ini internet Atau sosial media bahkan existed,
these officers used to communicate using encrypted messages
Ini petugas digunakan ke communicate Menggunakan terenkripsi pesan
in ways we can't even imagine today!
Di cara kita tidak bisa Bahkan bayangkan hari ini!
I've heard my father say...
Saya sudah Mendengar saya ayah katakan...
there was a time when these two held this nation together.
Sana sebuah waktu kapan ini dua Held ini bangsa bersama.
Even then, Daniel's mind didn't need supercomputers!
Bahkan lalu, Daniel pikiran tidak Perlu supercomputers!
And Rahim Sahib didn't need weapons to win a war!
Dan Rahim Tuan tidak perlu senjata Ke menang sebuah perang!
All these years, they weren't gathering followers,
Semua ini tahun, Mereka tidak mengumpulkan pengikut,
but faith!
Tapi faith!
Trust!
Percaya!
Do you realise what will happen if they join forces again?
Apa kamu Sadar apa akan terjadi Jika mereka join pasukan lagi?
Blast!
Ledakan!
I want to make my mark in that moment.
Saya ingin Buat saya tanda di situ moment.
I don't want to die! Find them!
Saya tidak mau Ke mati! Temukan mereka!
During a Naga insurgency operation he led in 2008,
Selama sebuah Naga insurgency operasi Dia memimpin di 2008,
Colonel Rahim lost a leg.
Kolonel Rahim hilang sebuah leg.
Twelve soldiers were killed in that mission.
Twelve tentara dibunuh di situ mission.
Why would Daniel trust someone like him?
Kenapa akan Daniel percaya Seseorang suka dia?
Because it was not his mistake! Damn it!
Karena itu tidak dia kesalahan! Sial itu!
That operation was never on records.
Itu operasi tidak pernah di rekam.
So, the Colonel took responsibility for those deaths.
Jadi, Kolonel mengambil tanggung jawab Untuk itu kematian.
Even Rahim Sahib's posting to the academy
Bahkan Rahim Tuan kiriman Ke akademi
was a form of punishment.
sebuah form dari punishment.
In front of teachers far junior to him,
Di front dari guru Jauh junior ke dia,
he worked as a mere instructor.
Dia bekerja sebagai sebuah mere instructor.
But everyone was against him.
Tapi semua orang terhadap dia.
That was the media narrative.
Itu media narrative.
But he really fought for their justice.
Tapi dia benar-benar fought Untuk mereka justice.
Finally, Rahim Sir proved to the government that it wasn't his mistake.
Akhirnya, Rahim Pak terbukti ke Pemerintah itu itu tidak dia kesalahan.
Unfortunately, no one reported it.
Sayangnya, tidak ada orang Laporan itu.
But Daniel...
Tapi Daniel...
given his current situation,
Diberi dia current situasi,
it's unlikely anyone other than Rahim Sahib would help him.
itu Unlikely siapa pun selain Rahim Tuan akan tolong dia.
There's another reason for that.
Ada Lain alasan untuk itu.
A secret...
Sebuah rahasia...
that very few know about.
Itu sangat sedikit tahu tentang.
Sir, Daniel has reached the location. Shall we go in?
Pak, Daniel sudah reached lokasi. Kita pergi Di?
Make sure he is inside...
Buat yakin dia di dalam...
and not armed.
Dan tidak armed.
Copy that, sir!
Salin itu, Pak!
Anju...
Anju...
for this one day, I need you to take care of Sir
Untuk ini satu hari, Saya perlu Kamu ke ambil peduli dari Pak
more than you've ever taken care of me.
Lebih daripada kamu sudah pernah Diambil peduli dari saya.
It's not a request.
Itu Tidak sebuah permintaan.
It's an order!
Itu Sebuah perintah!
Rahim, you'll have to handle this on your own.
Rahim, kamu akan harus handle Ini di kamu sendiri.
We've got far bigger storms to weather.
Kita sudah Mendapat jauh bigger storms Ke weather.
These kids are just amateurs.
Ini anak-anak hanya amateurs.
Until you cross Kathmandu,
Sampai kamu cross Kathmandu,
no one will intercept this ambulance.
tidak ada orang Akan intercept Ini ambulans.
Have a safe flight!
Punya sebuah aman penerbangan!
Sir, there's no response. Shall we break in?
Pak, ada tidak tanggapan. Akan kita break di?
Go ahead.
Pergi ahead.
Keep it low.
Simpan itu rendah.
Rahim Sahib...
Rahim Tuan...
Why are you helping Danny?
Kenapa apa kamu tolong Danny?
He's turned out to be a traitor.
Dia Putar keluar ke menjadi sebuah pengkhianat.
Sreedharan Sir...
Sreedharan Pak...
From the day our friendship began,
Dari hari Kita friendship began,
Danny has never once asked me for a favour.
Danny sudah tidak pernah sekali Bertanya saya untuk sebuah favour.
But when trouble strikes,
Tapi kapan masalah strikes,
having his back without being asked...
Punya dia kembali Tanpa sedang bertanya...
Isn't that a soldier's code, sir?
Tidak Itu sebuah tentara kode, Pak?
Since he needs to stay off the radar for a while,
Sejak dia perlu ke tinggal Mati radar sebentar,
I decided to take charge of this house and everything here.
Saya decided ke ambil tuduhan dari ini rumah Dan semuanya sini.
And this gun...
Dan ini senjata...
Because of the death threats from Maoists,
Karena dari kematian ancaman Dari Maoists,
your department issued me this pistol for self-defence.
Kamu department issued saya Ini pistol untuk diri-pertahanan.
But this gun can't tell...
Tapi ini senjata tidak bisa beri tahu...
if the attackers are Maoists
Jika attackers Maoists
or men from our own department.
Atau pria dari kita sendiri department.
Hey! You're wasting your time looking around, brother.
Hei! kamu Wasting kamu waktu Lihat sekitar, saudara laki-laki.
You're not going to find anything.
Kamu Tidak akan temukan apa pun.
Get your boys and clear out, sir.
Dapatkan kamu anak laki-laki dan jelas keluar, Pak.
You take care.
Kamu ambil peduli.
If it was Rahim Sahib who helped Daniel leave the country,
Jika itu Rahim Tuan Siapa tolong Daniel pergi negara,
even to bring him back,
Bahkan untuk membawa dia kembali,
he will be the key.
Dia akan menjadi key.
Sir, our team is at Daniel's Delhi apartment.
Pak, kita tim di Daniel Delhi apartemen.
Shall we go in?
Kita pergi Di?
Still the same old shit, man!
Masih sama lama shit, pria!
Sure, go in and check.
Yakin, pergi di dan periksa.
You won't find squat!
Kamu tidak akan temukan squat!
Hello?
Halo?
What happened?
Apa yang terjadi?
Why aren't you at school, dear?
Kenapa tidak kamu di sekolah, sayang?
Dad said I can take leave today!
Ayah berkata Saya bisa ambil pergi hari ini!
Why didn't you drop her off at school?
Kenapa tidak kamu jatuhkan dia Mati di sekolah?
Uma, I don't have time. I need to leave.
Uma, saya tidak punya waktu. Saya harus Pergi.
What's your problem, Michael?
Apa kamu masalah, Michael?
We were just trying to start over.
Kita hanya mencoba ke mulai atas.
If you're here, at least take responsibility for our daughter!
Jika kamu sini, setidaknya ambil Tanggung jawab untuk kita anak perempuan!
If you can't do that, this won't work.
Jika kamu bisa't lakukan itu, Ini tidak akan kerja.
Look, I don't think I can live an ordinary life anymore!
Lihat, Saya jangan pikir Saya bisa hidup Sebuah biasa hidup lagi!
I'm answerable to too many people.
Saya Answerable Ke juga banyak orang.
If I don't leave from here now,
Jika Saya jangan pergi dari sini sekarang,
your life won't be normal either.
Kamu hidup tidak akan menjadi normal salah satu.
How long will you live in fear of these people?
Bagaimana lama akan kamu hidup Di fear dari ini orang?
You're not willing to work anymore!
Kamu Tidak akan Ke kerja lagi!
Let's just go back to the way things were.
Biarkan hanya mundur Ke cara hal-hal.
Wouldn't that be better?
Tidak akan Itu menjadi lebih baik?
I'll never have the life I once had.
Saya akan Tidak pernah punya hidup Saya sekali sudah.
I want you and our daughter with me.
Saya ingin kamu dan kita Anak perempuan dengan saya.
But for that, you need to give me some time.
Tapi untuk itu, Kamu harus beri saya beberapa waktu.
I have to sort out a few things.
Saya harus Sort keluar sebuah sedikit hal-hal.
If possible,
Jika mungkin,
can you please drop me off?
bisakah kamu Tolong jatuhkan saya mati?
Please...
Tolong...
- Can I get this car? - Yes, sir.
- Bisa Saya dapatkan ini mobil? - Ya, Pak.
Sir, we need your Aadhaar card too.
Pak, kita perlu kamu Aadhaar card juga.
Won't my driving licence do?
Tidak akan Saya driving licence lakukan?
I'm afraid not, sir.
Saya Afraid tidak, Pak.
Sir, Michael's Aadhaar card has been scanned at Tevis Car Rentals, Bangalore!
Pak, Michael Aadhaar card sudah sudah Scanned di Tevis Mobil Rentals, Bangalore!
Shall we go?
Kita pergi?
That's it, guys.
Itu Itu, teman-teman.
They're on their way to Daniel.
Mereka Di mereka cara ke Daniel.
Will you take it on from here, Vignesh?
Akan kamu ambil itu di dari sini, Vignesh?
Did I ask you to take this road?
Melakukan Saya tanya kamu ke ambil ini jalan?
- It's a straight highway. - No, no. Take this round.
- itu Sebuah straight highway. - Tidak, tidak. Ambil ini round.
And exit.
Dan keluar.
Three rules!
Tiga rules!
No highways,
Tidak highways,
no tolls, and strictly...
Tidak tolls, dan ketat...
no Google Maps!
Tidak Google Maps!
Sir.
Pak.
Danny...
Danny...
Danny!
Danny!
Danny!!
Danny!!
Rahim...
Rahim...
Death...
Kematian...
I can see it staring right back at me.
Saya bisa lihat itu staring Benar kembali di saya.
- I'm running out of time, man! - Hey...
- saya Berjalan keluar dari waktu, pria! - Hei...
I'm here, right?
Saya Sini, benar?
Don't give up yet. Hang in there for me.
Jangan Beri atas belum. Hang di sana untuk saya.
I'm not going to let you die like this!
Saya tidak akan Biarkan kamu mati suka ini!
We need to shift Daniel immediately!
Kita harus giliran Daniel segera!
He needs a blood transfusion.
Dia perlu sebuah darah transfusion.
Sir...
Pak...
Sir, the car is currently stationed near St. Antony's Church,
Pak, mobil currently stationed Near St. Antony's Church,
in the Mangalore New Port area.
Di Mangalore Baru Port area.
If the car moves,
Jika mobil bergerak,
you can see it in this tracker.
kamu bisa Lihat itu di sini tracker.
It's been ages...
Itu Sudah ages...
since we hit the road like this together, Danny.
Sejak kita hit jalan Suka ini bersama, Danny.
Back in the day,
Kembali di hari,
we didn't need anyone's help to get around, did we?
Kita tidak perlu siapa pun tolong Ke dapatkan sekitar, melakukan kita?
Man, the things we've done!
Pria, hal-hal kita sudah selesai!
If I kick the bucket along the way,
Jika Saya kick bucket Bersama cara,
don't bother with a funeral.
jangan Bother dengan sebuah pemakaman.
Just dump me in a river
Hanya buang saya di sebuah river
or toss me off a cliff.
Atau toss saya mati sebuah cliff.
Ever since last night,
Pernah sejak lalu malam,
all you've been doing is harping on about dying.
Semua kamu sudah sudah melakukan Harping di tentang dying.
Shut up about death and say something else, man!
Diam Tentang kematian Dan katakan sesuatu lain, pria!
What's there to talk about living anyway?
Apa sana ke bicara Tentang hidup bagaimanapun?
I'm more worried about this guy.
Saya Lebih khawatir tentang ini pria.
Right?
Benar?
In the end, you might be the last one standing.
Di akhir, kamu mungkin menjadi lalu satu berdiri.
Do you think joining us was a mistake?
Lakukan kamu pikir Joining kita sebuah kesalahan?
No, sir.
Tidak, Pak.
What Jyothi couldn't finish…
Apa Jyothi tidak bisa finish…
shouldn't I see it through?
tidak seharusnya Saya lihat itu melalui?
I get these spasms every now and then.
Saya dapatkan ini spasms Setiap sekarang dan lalu.
Guess I've been idle too long, huh?
Guess saya sudah sudah idle juga lama, hah?
How did this happen, sir?
Bagaimana melakukan ini terjadi, Pak?
War!
Perang!
What else would it be?
Apa lagi Akan itu menjadi?
But... only to end up as a warrior this country didn't want.
Tapi... Hanya ke akhir atas sebagai sebuah warrior Ini negara tidak ingin.
Two bullets!
Dua bullets!
When there was no other option, they had to amputate it.
Kapan sana tidak lain option, Mereka sudah ke amputate itu.
I really should've just died on that field, right?
Saya benar-benar seharusnya sudah hanya meninggal di situ field, benar?
At least the others would've received what they deserved.
Setidaknya lain akan sudah Menerima apa mereka deserved.
Hey! Drop it, man!
Hei! Jatuhkan itu, pria!
That was years ago!
Itu tahun lalu!
You hate it when I talk about dying,
Kamu benci itu Kapan Saya bicara tentang dying,
but you can go on all you want, huh?
Tapi kamu bisa pergi di Semua kamu mau, hah?
Go faster! Closer!
Pergi lebih cepat! Closer!
Hey!
Hei!
Eyes on the road!
Mata di jalan!
Michael, whose car is this?
Michael, milik siapa mobil ini?
- I rented it, sir. - Hey!
- Saya rented itu, Pak. - Hei!
I'm avoiding Google Maps and toll booths
Saya Avoiding Google Maps Dan toll booths
so we leave no digital trail…
Jadi kita pergi tidak digital trail…
and you pull a stupid stunt like this?
Dan kamu tarik Sebuah stupid stunt suka ini?
Hey, take left!
Hei, ambil pergi!
Hey! Careful!
Hei! Careful!
Shit!
Shit!
Don't slow!
Jangan Lambat!
Danny...
Danny...
pass me my bag!
Pass saya saya tas!
Hey, it's them! Be careful!
Hei, itu mereka! Menjadi careful!
Yes.
Ya.
- Fast! Fast! - Yeah!
- Cepat! Cepat! - Ya!
Find the gun! Goddammit!
Temukan senjata! Goddammit!
- Danny! - Yes!
- Danny! - Ya!
- I'm still too weak for this! - Hey!
- saya Masih juga weak untuk ini! - Hei!
I'm not what I used to be. I need backup!
Saya tidak Apa Saya digunakan ke menjadi. Saya perlu backup!
Come on!
Ayo!
Come on! Jump!
Ayo! Jump!
Go now!
Pergi sekarang!
Sir! Sir!
Pak! Pak!
Go, go, go!
Pergi, pergi, pergi!
Shit!
Shit!
Danny, this is Captain Haridas.
Danny, ini Kapten Haridas.
He was part of my team.
Dia bagian dari saya tim.
We've sourced O+ blood for you from a blood bank
Kita sudah Sourced O+ darah untuk kamu Dari sebuah darah bank
in advance.
Di advance.
We've briefed your lead doctor and the nursing staff
Kita sudah Briefed kamu pimpin dokter Dan nursing staff
on the gravity of the situation.
Di gravity dari situasi.
At Lathika's request...
Di Lathika's permintaan...
the prison ward where they're holding that student
penjara bangsal di mana mereka Pegang itu mahasiswa
is being monitored by Haridas's men.
sedang dipantau Oleh Haridas's pria.
Rahim...
Rahim...
I'm going to be stuck here for a while.
Saya akan Menjadi stuck Sini sebentar.
There's no point in you staying here.
Ada Tidak poin Di kamu tinggal sini.
Nothing must happen to that girl at the Kochi hospital.
Tidak ada harus terjadi ke itu gadis Di Kochi rumah sakit.
You have to be there.
Kamu harus Menjadi sana.
Sir...
Pak...
Hello, Michael.
Halo, Michael.
Where are you now?
Di mana apa kamu sekarang?
Daniel's condition is quite serious.
Daniel condition quite serius.
There was an attempt on his life.
Sana sebuah attempt di dia hidup.
Luckily, he escaped.
Untungnya, dia escaped.
We have to retrieve him.
Kita harus retrieve dia.
What do you want me to do, sir?
Apa yang kamu Ingin saya ke lakukan, Pak?
[Rahim] All the military facilities
[Rahim] Semua militer facilities
are connected to a common server.
connected ke sebuah common server.
A full blood transfusion
Sebuah penuh darah transfusion
takes about 3.5 to 4 hours.
Ambil tentang 3.5 Ke 4 jam.
That means you'll get four hours
Itu berarti kamu akan dapatkan empat jam
to breach into their system and do the job!
Ke breach ke dalam mereka sistem Dan lakukan pekerjaan!
I've got the list of the latest phone numbers.
Saya sudah Mendapat daftar Dari terbaru telepon nomor.
What next?
Apa berikutnya?
Vlog No. 113.
Vlog Tidak. 113.
Vimathan here!
Vimathan sini!
For getting me back to my country without it costing me a penny,
Untuk mendapatkan saya kembali ke saya negara Tanpa itu costing saya sebuah penny,
I owe a huge thanks to my friend JPS.
Saya owe sebuah huge terima kasih Ke saya teman JPS.
But guys,
Tapi teman-teman,
I'm in bad shape.
Saya Di buruk shape.
I'm poisoned.
Saya Diracuni.
So, by the time this video ends,
Jadi, oleh waktu ini video akhir,
I might end up with facial palsy.
Saya mungkin akhir atas dengan facial palsy.
To prevent that, the doctors recommend
Ke prevent itu, dokter recommend
immediate dialysis.
Segera dialysis.
Up until now,
Atas sampai sekarang,
I haven't had the opportunity to give you
Saya belum sudah opportunity ke beri kamu
a proper demonstration of Periscope.
Sebuah proper demonstration Dari Periscope.
Today, I finally have the chance.
Hari ini, Saya akhirnya punya kesempatan.
And it's not just anyone's phone…
Dan itu tidak hanya siapa pun telepon…
Let's try hijacking the phone of the very same JPS
Biarkan coba hijacking telepon Dari sangat sama JPS
who did this to me.
Siapa melakukan ini ke saya.
What you're seeing here
Apa kamu lihat sini
is the list of phone numbers being sent to DRW's Periscope cell.
daftar telepon nomor Sedang mengirim ke DRW's Periscope cell.
As you can see,
Sebagai kamu bisa lihat,
it's a bundle of ten individual phone numbers.
itu Sebuah bundle dari sepuluh Individu telepon nomor.
I'm removing one at random
Saya Removing satu di random
and replacing it with JPS's phone number.
Dan replacing itu dengan JPS's telepon nomor.
The numbers are encrypted there.
Nomor terenkripsi sana.
Then, they're fed into the Periscope program.
Lalu, mereka fed ke dalam Periscope program.
What we need now
Apa kita perlu sekarang
is the kind of bait JPS can't help but click.
jenis dari bait JPS tidak bisa tolong tapi klik.
- Sir? - Any update?
- Pak? - Apa pun pembaruan?
Sir, there are other people helping him.
Pak, sana lain orang Tolong dia.
We're trying to track that car.
Kita Mencoba ke lacak itu mobil.
Is there any leak from our end?
Sana apa pun leak dari kita akhir?
No, sir. Never!
Tidak, Pak. Tidak pernah!
Is there any chance
Sana apa pun kesempatan
one of your team members spoke to the media?
Satu dari kamu tim members Spoke ke media?
No, sir. You can trust my team.
Tidak, Pak. Kamu bisa Percaya saya tim.
Anybody from our lab?
Anybody dari kita lab?
No, sir. Everything was through proper channel.
Tidak, Pak. Semuanya Melalui proper channel.
No one suspects a thing.
Tidak ada orang Tersangka sebuah hal.
Then where did we fail, Vignesh?
Lalu di mana melakukan kita fail, Vignesh?
Sir, we personally monitored the chemical levels.
Pak, kita personally dipantau kimia levels.
It was exactly the same that was used in Jyothi's case.
Itu tepat sama Itu digunakan di Jyothi kasus.
It's very hard to detect.
Itu Sangat sulit ke detect.
Daniel must have somehow managed to take the antidote.
Daniel harus punya somehow Managed ke ambil antidote.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have survived, sir.
Sebaliknya, dia tidak akan Punya survived, Pak.
The chemical they're referring to...
Kimia mereka referring ke...
is a nerve agent.
sebuah saraf agent.
If the antidote isn't taken
Jika antidote tidak diambil
within five minutes of it getting into your body,
Dalam lima menit Dari itu mendapatkan ke dalam kamu tubuh,
death is certain.
Kematian tertentu.
What kind of fools are you guys?
Apa jenis dari fools apa kamu teman-teman?
- Then find the-- - Sir, drink?
- Lalu temukan -- - Pak, minum?
Errr, no.
Errr, tidak.
Sir, please switch off your phone.
Pak, tolong switch mati teleponmu.
We're about to take off.
Kita Tentang ke ambil mati.
Thank you!
Terima kasih!
Sir, his phone has just switched to aeroplane mode.
Pak, dia telepon sudah hanya Switched ke aeroplane mode.
- What next? - Now...
- Apa berikutnya? - Sekarang...
get into his frickin' life!
Dapatkan ke dalam dia frickin' hidup!
Every message he's sent,
Setiap pesan dia mengirim,
every call he's made, every photo he's taken,
Setiap telepon dia membuat, Setiap foto dia diambil,
his bank transactions, videos, chats, emails...
Dia bank transactions, Video, chats, email...
Every file in there is a story written in blood.
Setiap file di sana sebuah cerita written di darah.
So...
Jadi...
beware, Michael.
Beware, Michael.
Jyothi will be in there too.
Jyothi akan menjadi di sana juga.
It's time for your redemption!
Itu Waktu untuk kamu redemption!
Sir...
Pak...
He posted it half an hour ago.
Dia kiriman itu half sebuah jam lalu.
He's claiming he got it from your phone.
Dia Claiming Dia mendapat itu dari teleponmu.
[JPS] Ask her to compromise the case for 2.5.
[JPS] Tanya dia ke compromise kasus untuk 2.5.
Or else, let's negotiate with her husband again.
Atau lain, biarkan negosiasi Dengan dia suami lagi.
Listen to our "honourable" minister proposing a payoff...
Dengar ke kita "honourable" menteri Proposing sebuah payoff...
to bury the sexual assault complaint against him for two and a half crores.
Ke bury seksual assault pengaduan Terhadap dia untuk dua dan sebuah half crore.
And if she doesn't budge,
Dan jika dia tidak budge,
his plan is to negotiate with her husband instead.
Dia rencana ke negosiasi Dengan dia suami sebagai gantinya.
Call our IT Cell!
Telepon kita IT Cell!
Make sure this video doesn't get out!
Buat yakin ini video tidak keluar!
This letter, signed by JPS,
Ini surat, ditandatangani oleh JPS,
is the release order for the chemical.
release perintah Untuk kimia.
The chemical reaction will be instantaneous.
Kimia reaction Akan menjadi instantaneous.
No chemical traces will be found in the autopsy.
Tidak kimia traces akan menjadi Menemukan di autopsy.
Cause of death: infection post surgery.
Cause dari kematian: Infeksi kiriman operasi.
[news] Protests erupt at the airport...
[Berita] Protests erupt di bandara...
[faint sounds of news playing on TV]
[Faint sounds dari berita main di TV]
Call the media and stop this bloody broadcast!
Telepon media dan berhenti Ini bloody broadcast!
Impossible, sir. It's everywhere!
Mustahil, Pak. Itu Everywhere!
[reporters shouting]
[Reporters berteriak]
Sir, the media is making a huge scene outside.
Pak, media membuat Sebuah huge adegan di luar.
Shall we wait or exit through the departure gate?
Akan kita tunggu atau keluar melalui keberangkatan gerbang?
Why should I do that? I'm not scared of any media trial.
Kenapa harus Saya lakukan itu? Saya tidak Scared dari apa pun media trial.
I will use the main exit!
Saya akan Gunakan utama keluar!
Sir.
Pak.
Go back! Go back! JPS, go back!
Mundur! mundur! JPS, mundur!
[sloganeering continues]
[Sloganeering continues]
Visiting hours are over.
Visiting jam atas.
The ward gates will close at 8 PM.
Bangsal gerbang Akan tutup di 8 PM.
Except for the bystanders with cards, everyone else must leave now.
Except untuk bystanders dengan cards, Semua orang lain harus pergi sekarang.
Sir, it's Satheeshan.
Pak, itu Satheeshan.
My shift is up,
Saya giliran atas,
but Binu is late again.
Tapi Binu terlambat lagi.
He's not answering his phone.
Dia Tidak jawab dia telepon.
What am I supposed to do, sir?
Apa Saya seharusnya ke lakukan, Pak?
Your shift must be ending now, right?
Kamu giliran harus menjadi Akhir sekarang, benar?
It ended ages ago! I'm just worried the replacement hasn't arrived.
Itu akhir ages lalu! saya Hanya khawatir replacement belum tiba.
I take it he's not answering his phone?
Saya ambil itu dia tidak Jawab dia telepon?
There are people here,
Sana orang sini,
just biding their time until you're gone
Hanya biding mereka waktu Sampai kamu pergi
so they can enter the ward.
Jadi mereka bisa enter bangsal.
I can see them.
Saya bisa lihat mereka.
Can you, sir?
Bisakah kamu, Pak?
There are three of them.
Sana tiga dari mereka.
Do you see that "bystander" over there?
Apa kamu Lihat itu "Bystander" atas sana?
He doesn't have a patient in this ward.
Dia tidak punya sebuah pasien di sini bangsal.
And that male nurse coming this way...
Dan itu male perawat Datang ini cara...
you wouldn't have seen him on shift earlier.
Kamu tidak akan punya terlihat dia Di giliran earlier.
He's wearing an ID,
Dia Wearing sebuah ID,
but the photo doesn't match.
Tapi foto tidak cocok.
As for that doctor who just started his shift...
Sebagai untuk itu dokter Siapa hanya mulai dia giliran...
Are you sure he's even a doctor, sir?
Apa kamu Yakin dia Bahkan sebuah dokter, Pak?
One of them will slip in
Satu dari mereka akan slip di
and kill that girl.
Dan bunuh itu gadis.
Will you be able to stop him?
Akan kamu menjadi able ke berhenti dia?
Binu, the one you called? He isn't coming.
Binu, satu kamu menelepon? Dia tidak datang.
And your chief won't be answering any more calls today.
Dan kamu kepala tidak akan menjadi Jawab apa pun lebih telepon hari ini.
If you open this door for me now,
Jika kamu buka ini pintu untuk saya sekarang,
I'll shift that girl.
Saya akan Giliran itu gadis.
Who are you?
Siapa kamu?
Colonel Rahim Nayik.
Kolonel Rahim Nayik.
'93 Maratha Regiment.
'93 Maratha Regiment.
Do we have a deal?
Lakukan kita sudah sebuah deal?
Please!
Tolong!
Hey!
Hei!
Who are you?
Siapa kamu?
Move aside!
Bergerak samping!
[Nurse] Who is it?
[Perawat] Siapa itu?
Who are you?
Siapa kamu?
Security!
Keamanan!
Didn't you hear me?
Tidak Kamu dengar saya?
Doctor!
Dokter!
- Who let you in here? - Shush!
- Siapa biarkan kamu di sini? - Shush!
This is an ICU ward!
Ini Sebuah ICU bangsal!
What are you doing?
Apa yang kamu Melakukan?
Security!
Keamanan!
Doctor, please call someone!
Dokter, tolong telepon seseorang!
- Hey! - Who are you people?
- Hei! - siapa kamu Orang?
Move aside!
Bergerak samping!
Sir, it was a stabbing.
Pak, itu sebuah stabbing.
He was stabbed multiple times.
Dia stabbed multiple waktu.
The cause of death is a wound to the neck.
Cause dari kematian sebuah wound ke neck.
The ASI has given a statement
ASI sudah diberi sebuah pernyataan
that the Colonel was helping him.
Itu Kolonel tolong dia.
So there are no issues with the formalities.
Jadi sana tidak masalah Dengan formalities.
You're free to take the body whenever you like.
Kamu Bebas ke ambil tubuh Kapan pun kamu suka.
To keep our motherland from being torn apart,
Ke simpan kita motherland Dari sedang torn terpisah,
he gave up his own leg in the line of duty.
Dia memberi atas dia sendiri leg Di baris dari duty.
Show him respect!
Tunjukkan dia hormat!
Sorry, sir. A funeral without a guard of honour--
Maaf, Pak. Sebuah pemakaman tanpa sebuah guard dari honour--
Who did this to Rahim?
Siapa melakukan ini ke Rahim?
I want to know that!
Saya ingin tahu itu!
He had warned me… that they'd make their way in.
Dia sudah warned saya… Itu they'd buat mereka cara di.
Everything just… happened so fast.
Semuanya hanya… terjadi jadi cepat.
The ones who left…
Satu siapa pergi…
scattered in different directions.
Scattered di berbeda directions.
Did they kidnap the girl…
Melakukan mereka kidnap gadis…
or kill her?
Atau bunuh dia?
I don't know… anything.
Saya tidak tahu… Apa pun.
Rahim is communicating!
Rahim communicating!
Rewind and play.
Rewind dan main.
A prisoner of war...
Sebuah prisoner dari perang...
in North Vietnam,
Di North Vietnam,
Commander Jeremiah Denton.
Commander Jeremiah Denton.
He blinked his eyes
Dia blinked dia mata
to the news cameras in a pattern.
Ke berita kamera Di sebuah pola.
That pattern was later decoded as "Torture".
Itu pola later Decoded sebagai "Torture".
'T' 'O' 'R'...
'T' 'O' 'R'...
'T' 'U' 'R' 'E'.
'T' 'U' 'R' 'E'.
Alphabet 'O',
Alfabet 'O',
Alphabet 'L',
Alfabet 'L',
Alphabet 'I',
Alfabet 'Saya',
'V',
'V',
'E',
'E',
Numeric '1',
Numeric '1',
'2',
'2',
Alphabet 'C'.
Alfabet 'C'.
OLIVE 12C.
Olive 12C.
Olive...
Olive...
That's...
Itu...
That's the apartment where Jyothi used to stay.
Itu apartemen Di mana Jyothi digunakan ke tinggal.
Vlog number 114.
Vlog nomor 114.
Vimathan here.
Vimathan sini.
Today,
Hari ini,
I'm not the one who'll be doing the talking.
Saya tidak satu Who'll menjadi melakukan bicara.
It'll be two other people.
It'll menjadi dua lain orang.
The Victim...
Korban...
and The Predator!
Dan Predator!
Think of this as your chance to speak up.
Pikir dari ini sebagai kamu kesempatan ke bicara atas.
To everyone who pointed fingers at you...
Ke semua orang siapa Poin fingers di kamu...
cast you aside...
Cast kamu samping...
It's time to stand your ground and respond with courage.
Itu Waktu ke berdiri kamu darat Dan tanggapi dengan courage.
In 10th grade,
Di 10th nilai,
I got an A+.
Saya mendapat sebuah Sebuah+.
I was given the laptop...
Saya diberi laptop...
midway through 11th grade.
Midway melalui 11th nilai.
At first,
Di pertama,
I used it only for my studies.
Saya digunakan itu hanya untuk saya studi.
But eventually,
Tapi eventually,
we started using it to watch movies and the news.
Kita mulai menggunakan itu Ke lihat film dan berita.
My dad didn't even know what entrance exams were,
Saya ayah tidak bahkan tahu Apa entrance exams,
yet he still signed me up for NEET coaching.
Belum dia masih ditandatangani saya atas Untuk NEET coaching.
During the laptop distribution phase itself,
Selama laptop Distribution phase itself,
a surveillance system...
Sebuah pengawasan sistem...
was already pre-installed on them.
sudah pre-dipasang Di mereka.
The company used it to track the specific struggles of every household.
Perusahaan digunakan itu ke lacak specific struggles dari setiap household.
And in this case,
Dan di sini kasus,
it was Athira's coaching fees.
Itu Athira's coaching fees.
Forcing people into a new loan just to pay off
Forcing orang ke dalam sebuah baru pinjaman Hanya ke bayar mati
the interest on the previous one.
interest di previous satu.
Shakti's major revenue
Shakti besar revenue
comes from these call centres.
Datang dari ini telepon centres.
Since there's minimal documentation required,
Sejak ada minimal Documentation diperlukan,
people are easily drawn in.
Orang easily ditarik di.
An amount like that is just peanuts for a company like Shakti, right?
Sebuah amount suka itu hanya Peanuts untuk sebuah perusahaan suka Shakti, benar?
That's exactly where
Itu Tepat di mana
everyone gets it wrong.
Semua orang dapatkan itu salah.
10.2% of the total population is Below the Poverty Line (BPL).
10.2% Dari total population Bawah Poverty Baris (BPL).
And they are all eligible
Dan mereka semua eligible
for this laptop scheme.
Untuk ini laptop skema.
Whenever I have to change my clothes at home,
Kapan pun saya harus ubah Saya clothes di rumah,
my father and brother have to step outside.
Saya ayah dan saudara laki-laki harus Langkah di luar.
At that point,
Di situ poin,
that someone might be watching me through the laptop...
Itu seseorang mungkin menjadi Lihat saya melalui laptop...
how was I to know?
Bagaimana Saya ke tahu?
Shame...
Malu...
is greater than guilt.
greater daripada guilt.
Shame is exactly what Shakti targets.
Malu tepat apa Shakti targets.
The fear of being shamed
Fear dari sedang shamed
drives people to repay whatever the company demands.
Drives orang ke repay Apa pun perusahaan demands.
And as for those who can't pay...
Dan sebagai untuk itu siapa tidak bisa bayar...
My mother spoke out...
Saya ibu spoke keluar...
about the online loan my dad had taken,
Tentang online pinjaman Saya ayah sudah diambil,
and the threats he had been receiving.
Dan ancaman Dia sudah sudah receiving.
The police said they were taking me for counselling.
Polisi Berkata mereka Mengambil saya untuk counselling.
But instead, they blamed me for my father's death!
Tapi sebagai gantinya, mereka blamed saya Untuk saya ayah kematian!
Had I known this then,
Sudah Saya diketahui ini lalu,
I too would have followed my father.
Saya juga akan punya Ikuti saya ayah.
Come on!
Ayo!
Sir, Shakti's Kochi office is about to be raided!
Pak, Shakti Kochi kantor tentang ke menjadi raided!
- It's better to inform him. - Then do something!
- itu Lebih baik ke inform dia. - Lalu lakukan sesuatu!
Delay it!
Delay itu!
Everyone, cut your calls!
Semua orang, potong kamu telepon!
Remove the CPUs!
Hapus CPUs!
Take out the hard disks, thrash it!
Ambil keluar sulit disks, Thrash itu!
Don't just stand there gaping like morons!
Jangan Hanya berdiri sana Gaping suka morons!
Take this out! Take this out now!
Ambil ini keluar! Ambil ini keluar sekarang!
Now! Fast!
Sekarang! Cepat!
And break it!
Dan break itu!
Do it!
Lakukan itu!
Dad, if its about the raid,
Ayah, jika itu tentang raid,
I already know about it.
Saya sudah tahu tentang itu.
Don't discuss anything over the phone!
Jangan Bahas apa pun Atas telepon!
Do you hear me?
Apa kamu Dengar saya?
Hey... when are you going to realise the situation?
Hei... Kapan apa kamu pergi Ke sadar situasi?
I am out!
Saya Keluar!
They've already launched an internal inquiry against me.
They've sudah launched Sebuah internal inquiry terhadap saya.
And till then,
Dan till lalu,
I've been "advised" to leave the country.
Saya sudah Sudah "advised" Ke pergi negara.
When I return, I won't be a minister anymore!
Kapan Saya return, Saya tidak akan menjadi sebuah menteri lagi!
Please, just listen to me, Dad!
Tolong, hanya dengarkan saya, Ayah!
We'll talk later. Not over the phone!
Kita akan Bicara later. Tidak atas telepon!
If not now, when will you ever stand by me?
Jika tidak sekarang, Kapan akan kamu pernah berdiri oleh saya?
Dad, just shut your mouth and listen to me!
Ayah, hanya diam kamu mulut Dan dengarkan saya!
Don't you get it, even after everything that's happened in your life today?
Jangan Kamu dapatkan itu, bahkan setelah semuanya itu Terjadi di kamu hidup hari ini?
Your friend is listening!
Kamu teman dengar!
Daniel Sir...
Daniel Pak...
You can hear everything, right?
Kamu bisa Dengar semuanya, benar?
[sloganeering]
[Sloganeering]
I'm sorry, sir.
Saya Maaf, Pak.
I underestimated you.
Saya underestimated kamu.
Michael is with you, isn't he?
Michael dengan kamu, tidak dia?
He knows that
Dia tahu itu
I recruit programmers with a specific age.
Saya recruit programmers Dengan sebuah specific age.
Below 40s... for a sharper brain!
Bawah 40s... Untuk sebuah sharper brain!
But you...
Tapi kamu...
you've proven all my calculations wrong.
kamu sudah Proven semua Saya calculations salah.
JPS's life...
JPS's hidup...
To destroy my father's life...
Ke destroy saya ayah hidup...
all you needed was four hours.
Semua kamu butuh empat jam.
I admire you, sir!
Saya admire kamu, Pak!
Shakti... Just... Just stop it!
Shakti... Hanya... Hanya berhenti itu!
Dad... Please!
Ayah... Tolong!
It's the same old scenario.
Itu sama lama scenario.
Daniel Sir and Michael are together...
Daniel Pak dan Michael bersama...
And I am alone...
Dan saya sendiri...
struggling to survive.
Struggling ke bertahan.
You made me survive that day, sir.
Kamu membuat saya bertahan itu hari, Pak.
But you don't know what my father did, do you?
Tapi kamu jangan tahu Apa saya ayah melakukan, apa kamu?
Minister JPS is on the line.
Menteri JPS di baris.
FO's father.
FO's ayah.
Daniel sir...
Daniel Pak...
You don't have to save him just because he's my son.
Kamu tidak perlu selamatkan dia Hanya karena dia saya anak laki-laki.
He has violated his training protocol.
Dia sudah violated dia pelatihan protocol.
If his fate is to die,
Jika dia fate ke mati,
let him die.
Biarkan dia mati.
Viper reporting cockpit fire!
Viper laporan kokpit tembak!
Requesting permission for emergency landing!
Permintaan izin untuk pendaratan darurat!
That cockpit fire was no accident.
Itu kokpit tembak tidak accident.
My father created it.
Saya ayah created itu.
Do you know why?
Lakukan kamu tahu kenapa?
Elections were coming.
Pemilu datang.
The party wasn't confirming JPS's ticket.
Partai tidak Konfirmasi JPS's tiket.
But if his son died...
Tapi jika dia anak laki-laki meninggal...
especially during military training...
Especially selama Militer pelatihan...
his seat would be assured based on that sentiment.
Dia kursi akan menjadi assured Berdasarkan di situ sentiment.
Right, Dad?
Benar, Ayah?
Shakti, stop it!
Shakti, berhenti itu!
Stop it! You're crossing the limit!
Berhenti itu! Kamu Crossing limit!
That's what really happened, sir.
Itu Apa benar-benar terjadi, Pak.
You can check with Michael.
Kamu bisa Periksa dengan Michael.
The HUD was tampered with.
HUD tampered dengan.
That's why the cockpit caught fire.
Itu Kenapa kokpit caught tembak.
I reported it, but nobody listened.
Saya laporan itu, Tapi nobody dengar.
This is the only reason Michael stood by me for so long.
Ini Hanya alasan Michael berdiri oleh saya untuk jadi lama.
Isn't that right?
Tidak Itu benar?
No, no! All those are just your assumptions!
Tidak, tidak! Semua itu Hanya kamu assumptions!
You made a mistake, and I brought you back!
Kamu membuat sebuah kesalahan, Dan Saya membawa kamu kembali!
That is what happened!
Itu apa yang terjadi!
Stop it, Dad!
Berhenti itu, Ayah!
Do you want to know anything more now?
Apa kamu ingin tahu Apa pun lebih sekarang?
Just like you decided my fate back then...
Hanya suka kamu decided Saya fate kembali lalu...
today, I'll do the talking and you will listen!
Hari ini, saya akan lakukan bicara Dan kamu akan dengar!
Salvaging this won't be easy, Dad.
Salvaging ini tidak akan Menjadi mudah, Ayah.
So, for my sake...
Jadi, untuk saya sake...
so that I can stay alive today...
Jadi itu Saya bisa tinggal hidup hari ini...
I'm demanding this in return!
Saya Demanding ini di return!
Just think about it, Dad.
Hanya pikir tentang itu, Ayah.
If you want a statue raised in your honour...
Jika kamu mau sebuah statue Raised di kamu honour...
or a road named after you,
Atau sebuah jalan named setelah kamu,
I want you to die.
Saya ingin kamu ke mati.
You can't afford to lose, Dad.
Kamu bisa'T afford ke kehilangan, Ayah.
Where are you now, Dad?
Di mana apa kamu sekarang, Ayah?
Son... I am in our library.
Anak laki-laki... saya Di kita library.
There's that famous photograph of ours, right?
Ada Itu famous photograph Dari milik kita, benar?
Can you walk towards it?
Bisakah kamu Jalan menuju itu?
Once you're there...
Sekali kamu sana...
open the rack.
Buka rack.
[Daniel] Towards your left, in the emergency control panel,
[Daniel] Menuju kamu pergi, Di darurat kendali panel,
there is a Jettison lever.
ada sebuah Buang lever.
It's your personal pistol.
Itu Kamu pribadi pistol.
Browning 9mm.
Browning 9mm.
It's loaded, Dad.
Itu Muat, Ayah.
But sir, I've never done that before!
Tapi Pak, Saya sudah Tidak pernah selesai itu sebelum!
Do you trust me?
Apa kamu percaya saya?
Do you trust me, Dad?
Apa kamu percaya saya, Ayah?
Push the throttle hard in the Z axis!
Push throttle sulit Di Z axis!
Pull the trigger.
Tarik trigger.
Daniel sir...
Daniel Pak...
Didn't you hear that gun shot?
Tidak Kamu dengar itu senjata tembakan?
Thank you for the motivation!
Terima kasih Untuk motivation!
It was my father who'd been holding me back all this time.
Itu saya ayah who'd sudah Pegang saya kembali semua ini waktu.
If I can get rid of him with a single phone call...
Jika Saya bisa dapatkan rid dari dia Dengan sebuah satu panggilan telepon...
what harm could a girl's statement possibly bring me?
Apa harm bisa sebuah gadis Pernyataan possibly bawa saya?
Huh?
Hah?
Delete all files leading to Micheal, Jyothi,
Hapus semua file pimpin ke Micheal, Jyothi,
Daniel and Rahim right now!
Daniel dan Rahim sekarang juga!
Sir...
Pak...
Micheal is here!
Micheal sini!
His user ID just logged in.
Dia user ID hanya logged di.
Mike!
Mike!
I know you are here!
Saya tahu kamu sini!
Why did you do it?
Kenapa melakukan kamu lakukan itu?
I thought we were a team, bro!
Saya pikir kita sebuah tim, bro!
We started all this together, didn't we?
Kita mulai semua ini bersama, tidak Kita?
We only started it together.
Kita hanya mulai itu bersama.
But I'm ending this...
Tapi saya akhir ini...
on my own!
Di saya sendiri!
I told you to silence Jyothi!
Sudah saya bilang Ke diam Jyothi!
You didn't listen, right?
Kamu tidak dengar, benar?
I begged you to give her a chance!
Saya begged kamu Ke beri dia sebuah kesempatan!
You didn't listen, Shakti!
Kamu tidak dengar, Shakti!
Shakti!
Shakti!
You still have got a chance.
Kamu masih punya mendapat sebuah kesempatan.
Admit your mistakes!
Admit kamu kesalahan!
Daniel sir,
Daniel Pak,
mistake is yours!
Kesalahan milikmu!
You should've let me die that day!
Kamu harus'Ve biarkan saya Mati itu hari!
Right, dude?
Benar, dude?
I wanted you back...
Saya ingin kamu kembali...
as a fighter, as a human being!
Sebagai sebuah fighter, sebagai sebuah manusia sedang!
But you have no right to kill people!
Tapi kamu punya tidak benar Ke bunuh orang!
I still fight alone, Danny sir.
Saya masih lawan sendiri, Pak Danny.
I still fight alone, Danny sir!
Saya masih lawan sendiri, Pak Danny!
The last parcel Jyothi received was a bottle of perfume.
Lalu parcel Jyothi menerima sebuah botol dari perfume.
Is it still here somewhere?
Itu masih sini somewhere?
I have an approver.
Saya sudah Sebuah approver.
Presenting the evidence he has gathered as Exhibit 23 here.
Menyajikan bukti Dia sudah gathered sebagai Exhibit 23 sini.
This program in the student laptop scheme...
Ini program di mahasiswa laptop skema...
Is that similar to Periscope?
Itu similar ke Periscope?
Objection to her question!
Objection ke dia pertanyaan!
Answer me, Michael!
Jawab saya, Michael!
Is that similar to Periscope?
Itu similar ke Periscope?
Objection!
Objection!
- Michael, you don't have to-- - This is my time!
- Michael, kamu tidak perlu-- - ini Saya waktu!
And Micheal will answer that!
Dan Micheal akan jawab itu!
Michael, we have signed an NDA.
Michael, kita sudah ditandatangani sebuah NDA.
You read it thoroughly before signing, right?
Kamu read itu thoroughly Sebelum signing, benar?
- We will have to sue you for-- - Shut your mouth!
- Kita akan harus sue kamu untuk-- - Diam kamu mulut!
Do you own this court?
Apa kamu Sendiri ini pengadilan?
Athira is my client and Micheal will speak!
Athira saya client Dan Micheal akan bicara!
[Judge] Overruled!
[Hakim] Overruled!
Now answer me, Michael.
Sekarang jawab saya, Michael.
They're both the same program.
Mereka Keduanya sama program.
I recoded it for Shakti.
Saya recoded itu untuk Shakti.
[Daniel] The battle that Nalini Madam began,
[Daniel] battle itu Nalini Bu began,
has finally been won through Athira.
Sudah akhirnya sudah menang Melalui Athira.
Only age divides them.
Hanya age divides mereka.
One succumbed to death,
Satu succumbed ke kematian,
while the other resisted and fought her way to victory.
Saat lain resisted Dan fought dia cara ke victory.
The court praised Athira for her courage to speak out...
Pengadilan praised Athira Untuk dia courage ke bicara keluar...
even at the risk of losing her dignity.
Bahkan di risiko Dari losing dia dignity.
The court ruled that her future studies
Pengadilan ruled itu Dia future studi
are now the government's responsibility.
sekarang pemerintah tanggung jawab.
The order mandated a total recall
Perintah mandated sebuah total recall
of every laptop issued by Shakti Group to date,
Dari setiap laptop issued Oleh Shakti Group ke tanggal,
replacing them with new systems that ensure the safety of our children.
Replacing mereka dengan baru sistem Itu pastikan keselamatan dari kita anak-anak.
Trust you got the passport, Danny.
Percaya kamu mendapat paspor, Danny.
I never asked for it, sir.
Saya tidak pernah bertanya untuk itu, Pak.
Government wants you back, Danny.
Pemerintah ingin kamu kembali, Danny.
Sir!
Pak!
Should we seal this off now?
Harus kita seal ini mati sekarang?
Rahim must be given the respect he deserves.
Rahim harus menjadi diberi hormat dia deserves.
Make that happen first, sir.
Buat itu terjadi pertama, Pak.
What do you mean?
Apa yang kamu Maksud?
Colonel Rahim is a martyr!
Kolonel Rahim sebuah martyr!
I want to see his name
Saya ingin Lihat dia nama
on the National War Memorial!
Di National Perang Memorial!
I reckon it will be difficult for you.
Saya reckon itu akan menjadi Sulit untuk kamu.
But I'll only step into that office once I see it there.
Tapi saya akan hanya langkah ke dalam itu kantor Sekali Saya lihat itu sana.
Let it stay there, man.
Biarkan itu tinggal sana, pria.
Having it there...
Punya itu sana...
makes me believe he's still around!
Buat saya percaya dia Masih sekitar!
It gives me strength.
Itu beri saya strength.
♪ Searing memories of our yesterdays, within my heart will always stay ♪
♪ Searing memories dari kita kemarin, Dalam saya heart akan selalu tinggal ♪
♪ O my fellow traveller, who vanishes into the distance today ♪
♪ O saya fellow traveller, Siapa vanishes ke dalam distance hari ini ♪
♪ On the paths we traversed throughout the years ♪
♪ Di paths kita traversed Throughout tahun ♪
♪ Through all of the days, the joys, and the fears ♪
♪ Melalui semua dari hari, joys, dan fears ♪
♪ My feet never stumbled, never did I fall ♪
♪ Saya feet tidak pernah stumbled, Tidak pernah melakukan Saya jatuh ♪
♪ For I know your steady hand was the reason for it all ♪
♪ Untuk Saya tahu kamu steady tangan alasan untuk itu semua ♪
♪ As the golden sun takes his leave of the sky ♪
♪ Sebagai golden sun Ambil dia pergi dari sky ♪
♪ O great ocean... do not let your waters run dry ♪
♪ O bagus ocean... jangan Biarkan kamu waters lari kering ♪
♪ O great ocean ♪
♪ O bagus ocean ♪
♪ Like a synonym for a smile's gentle grace ♪
♪ Suka sebuah synonym Untuk sebuah smile's gentle grace ♪
♪ Is your ever-familiar and timeless face ♪
♪ kamu pernah-familiar Dan timeless wajah ♪
♪ My beloved friend's face ♪
♪ Saya beloved teman wajah ♪
It's because of you
Itu Karena dari kamu
we got the program back in the system, Danny.
Kita mendapat program Kembali di sistem, Danny.
They have accepted all your demands.
Mereka punya menerima semua kamu demands.
The chief wants you back, Danny.
Kepala ingin kamu kembali, Danny.
He said you are a great Indian!
Dia berkata kamu sebuah bagus India!
Great Indian what?
Bagus India apa?
Well, he didn't say that.
Baiklah, dia tidak katakan itu.
Sir, do you remember
Pak, apa kamu ingat
when we first installed CCTV cameras here in Delhi?
Kapan kita pertama dipasang CCTV kamera sini di Delhi?
We filed an affidavit in court that day...
Kita diajukan sebuah affidavit Di pengadilan itu hari...
stating that under no circumstances would that footage be misused,
Stating itu bawah tidak circumstances Akan itu footage menjadi misused,
and the common man's privacy would be protected at all costs.
Dan common pria privasi Akan menjadi protected di semua costs.
Does that still hold true?
Melakukan itu masih pegang benar?
So what should I tell the chief?
Jadi apa harus Saya beri tahu kepala?
Tell him to complete the sentence.
Beri tahu dia ke lengkap sentence.
Who am I?
Siapa Saya?
The great Indian traitor...
Bagus India pengkhianat...
or...
Atau...
Patriot?
Patriot?
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
He speaks from a room that has forgotten its own walls.
Dia bicara dari sebuah ruangan Itu sudah forgotten itu sendiri walls.
Every surface, they say, Has become an ear
Setiap surface, mereka katakan, Sudah become sebuah ear
Every silence, they say, Is being collected
Setiap diam, mereka katakan, Sedang collected
He invented windows to look at the world
Dia invented jendela Ke lihat di dunia
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
♪ O, alien oasis ♪
But now, it seems, the windows are watching him
Tapi sekarang, itu sepertinya, jendela lihat dia
It seems the wind that gushes in through those windows,
Itu sepertinya wind itu gushes Di melalui itu jendela,
absorbs his secrets along with his sweat
Absorbs dia rahasia Bersama dengan dia sweat
His name is "Human"
Dia nama "Manusia"
♪ O, Alien Oasis... O, garden of illusions and secrets ♪
♪ O, Alien Oasis... O, garden dari illusions dan rahasia ♪
♪ Have the butterflies arrived in soft delusions ♪
♪ Punya butterflies tiba Di lembut delusions ♪
♪ Unaware of the fire, drawn by desire ♪
♪ Tidak sadar dari tembak, Ditarik oleh keinginan ♪
♪ Only to be consumed by that fire ♪
♪ Hanya ke menjadi dikonsumsi Oleh itu tembak ♪
The room was never a room,
Ruangan tidak pernah sebuah ruangan,
but a stall in a farm.
Tapi sebuah stall di sebuah peternakan.
For someone to milk dry, and when yield fails, to be slaughtered
Untuk seseorang ke milk kering, Dan kapan yield fails, ke menjadi slaughtered
Not a dystopian animal farm.
Tidak sebuah dystopian animal peternakan.
But where he, his kind,
Tapi di mana dia, dia jenis,
you, and I all reside:
Kamu, dan Saya semua reside:
A real Human Farm.
Sebuah nyata Manusia Peternakan.